{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "toys", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "biggest", "object": "toys", "location": "on the side table"}], "plan": "navigate to on the side table -> detect_object biggest toys at on the side table -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "heaviest", "toys", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "heaviest", "object": "toys", "location": "on the desk"}], "plan": "navigate to on the desk -> detect_object heaviest toys at on the desk -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "bathroom", "then", "locate", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "right", "arm", "and", "guide", "them", "to", "the", "drinks", "bar"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "navigate", "location": "bathroom"}, {"intent": "locate", "person": "person", "filter": "right arm"}, {"intent": "guide", "location": "drinks bar"}], "plan": "navigate to bathroom -> detect_person with right arm -> navigate to drinks bar -> guide_person to drinks bar"}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "cans", "in", "the", "bedroom", "then", "get", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "left", "arm", "in", "the", "bedroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "locate", "object": "cans", "location": "bedroom"}, {"intent": "get"}, {"intent": "deliver", "recipient": "person", "filter": "left arm", "location": "bedroom"}], "plan": "navigate to bedroom -> detect_object cans at bedroom -> grasp -> navigate to bedroom -> deliver cans to person"}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "book", "in", "the", "living", "room", "then", "grasp", "it", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "locate", "object": "book", "location": "living room"}, {"intent": "grasp"}, {"intent": "bring", "recipient": "me"}], "plan": "navigate to living room -> detect_object book at living room -> grasp -> deliver book to me"}
{"tokens": ["greet", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "yellow", "t", "shirt", "in", "the", "terrace", "and", "guide", "them", "to", "the", "bedroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "greet", "person": "yellow t shirt", "filter": "wearing", "location": "terrace"}, {"intent": "guide", "location": "bedroom"}], "plan": "navigate to terrace -> greet_person yellow t shirt with wearing at terrace -> navigate to bedroom -> guide_person to bedroom"}
{"tokens": ["lead", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "orange", "jacket", "from", "the", "workshop", "to", "the", "workshop"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "lead", "person": "orange jacket", "filter": "wearing", "location": "workshop"}], "plan": "navigate to workshop -> guide_person orange jacket to workshop"}
{"tokens": ["bring", "me", "a", "tablet", "from", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "bring", "recipient": "me", "object": "tablet", "location": "shelf"}], "plan": "navigate to shelf -> grasp -> navigate to shelf -> deliver tablet to me"}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "study", "then", "meet", "Rosa", "and", "say", "your", "teams", "name"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-VERB", "B-CONTENT", "I-CONTENT", "I-CONTENT"], "slots": [{"intent": "go", "location": "study"}, {"intent": "meet", "person": "Rosa"}, {"intent": "say", "content": "your teams name"}], "plan": "navigate to study -> meet_person Rosa -> greet_person"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "plate", "there", "are", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "plate", "location": "on the counter"}], "plan": "navigate to on the counter -> count plate at on the counter -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "thinnest", "object", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "thinnest", "location": "on the shelf"}], "plan": "navigate to on the shelf -> detect_object thinnest at on the shelf -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "lightest", "object", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "lightest", "location": "on the shelf"}], "plan": "navigate to on the shelf -> detect_object lightest at on the shelf -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "standing", "person", "in", "the", "closet", "and", "escort", "them", "to", "the", "workshop"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "find", "filter": "standing", "person": "person", "location": "closet"}, {"intent": "escort", "location": "workshop"}], "plan": "navigate to closet -> detect_person with pose standing at closet -> navigate to workshop -> guide_person to workshop"}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "desk", "then", "locate", "a", "cans", "and", "get", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "Karen", "in", "the", "storage", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "navigate", "location": "desk"}, {"intent": "locate", "object": "cans"}, {"intent": "get"}, {"intent": "deliver", "recipient": "Karen", "location": "storage room"}], "plan": "navigate to desk -> detect_object cans -> grasp -> navigate to storage room -> deliver cans to Karen"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "smallest", "object", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "smallest", "location": "on the desk"}], "plan": "navigate to on the desk -> detect_object smallest at on the desk -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["salute", "the", "person", "wearing", "an", "orange", "t", "shirt", "in", "the", "laundry", "room", "and", "tell", "the", "time"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT"], "slots": [{"intent": "salute", "person": "orange t shirt", "filter": "wearing", "location": "laundry room"}, {"intent": "tell", "content": "time"}], "plan": "navigate to laundry room -> greet_person orange t shirt with wearing at laundry room -> tell time"}
{"tokens": ["get", "a", "remotes", "from", "the", "desk", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "get", "object": "remotes", "location": "desk"}, {"intent": "bring", "recipient": "me"}], "plan": "navigate to desk -> grasp -> deliver remotes to me"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "the", "pose", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "garden", "table", "to", "the", "person", "at", "the", "bathroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "content": "pose", "person": "person", "location": "bathroom"}], "plan": "navigate to bathroom -> tell pose"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "bottle", "there", "are", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "bottle", "location": "on the desk"}], "plan": "navigate to on the desk -> count bottle at on the desk -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["grasp", "a", "plates", "from", "the", "desk", "and", "place", "it", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "grasp", "object": "plates", "location": "desk"}, {"intent": "place", "location": "on the counter"}], "plan": "navigate to desk -> grasp -> navigate to on the counter -> place at on the counter"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "cup", "there", "are", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "cup", "location": "on the garden table"}], "plan": "navigate to on the garden table -> count cup at on the garden table -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "closet", "are", "wearing", "blue", "shirts"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "blue shirts", "location": "closet", "filter": "wearing"}], "plan": "navigate to closet -> detect_person with wearing at closet -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "glass", "there", "are", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "glass", "location": "on the garden table"}], "plan": "navigate to on the garden table -> count glass at on the garden table -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["escort", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "gray", "t", "shirt", "from", "the", "garage", "to", "the", "office"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "escort", "person": "gray t shirt", "filter": "wearing", "location": "office"}], "plan": "navigate to office -> guide_person gray t shirt to office"}
{"tokens": ["escort", "Sam", "from", "the", "garden", "to", "the", "laundry", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "escort", "person": "Sam", "location": "laundry room"}], "plan": "navigate to laundry room -> guide_person Sam to laundry room"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "object", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "biggest", "location": "on the counter"}], "plan": "navigate to on the counter -> detect_object biggest at on the counter -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Tom", "in", "the", "workshop", "and", "follow", "them", "to", "the", "office"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "meet", "person": "Tom", "location": "workshop"}, {"intent": "follow", "location": "office"}], "plan": "navigate to workshop -> meet_person Tom at workshop -> navigate to office -> guide_person to office"}
{"tokens": ["bring", "me", "a", "plate", "from", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "bring", "recipient": "me", "object": "plate", "location": "side table"}], "plan": "navigate to side table -> grasp -> navigate to side table -> deliver plate to me"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "workshop", "are", "wearing", "orange", "coats"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "orange coats", "location": "workshop", "filter": "wearing"}], "plan": "navigate to workshop -> detect_person with wearing at workshop -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "study", "then", "find", "a", "box", "and", "grasp", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "Rosa", "in", "the", "workshop"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "navigate", "location": "study"}, {"intent": "find", "object": "box"}, {"intent": "grasp"}, {"intent": "deliver", "recipient": "Rosa", "location": "workshop"}], "plan": "navigate to study -> detect_object box -> grasp -> navigate to workshop -> deliver box to Rosa"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "largest", "bottles", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "largest", "object": "bottles", "location": "on the garden table"}], "plan": "navigate to on the garden table -> detect_object largest bottles at on the garden table -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "can", "there", "are", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "can", "location": "on the side table"}], "plan": "navigate to on the side table -> count can at on the side table -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["follow", "Olivia", "from", "the", "terrace", "to", "the", "garden"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "follow", "person": "Olivia", "location": "garden"}], "plan": "navigate to garden -> guide_person Olivia to garden"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "thinnest", "mugs", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "thinnest", "object": "mugs", "location": "on the counter"}], "plan": "navigate to on the counter -> detect_object thinnest mugs at on the counter -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "lightest", "object", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "lightest", "location": "on the counter"}], "plan": "navigate to on the counter -> detect_object lightest at on the counter -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["take", "a", "bottles", "from", "the", "shelf", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "take", "object": "bottles", "location": "shelf"}, {"intent": "bring", "recipient": "me"}], "plan": "navigate to shelf -> grasp -> deliver bottles to me"}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "toy", "in", "the", "study", "then", "get", "it", "and", "place", "it", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "locate", "object": "toy", "location": "study"}, {"intent": "get"}, {"intent": "place", "location": "on the garden table"}], "plan": "navigate to study -> detect_object toy at study -> grasp -> navigate to on the garden table -> place at on the garden table"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "entrance", "are", "wearing", "white", "jackets"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "white jackets", "location": "entrance", "filter": "wearing"}], "plan": "navigate to entrance -> detect_person with wearing at entrance -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Ingrid", "at", "the", "study", "then", "find", "them", "in", "the", "closet"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "meet", "person": "Ingrid", "location": "study"}, {"intent": "find", "location": "closet"}], "plan": "navigate to study -> meet_person Ingrid at study -> navigate to closet"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "kitchen", "are", "wearing", "white", "t", "shirts"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "white t shirts", "location": "kitchen", "filter": "wearing"}], "plan": "navigate to kitchen -> detect_person with wearing at kitchen -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "smallest", "object", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "smallest", "location": "on the desk"}], "plan": "navigate to on the desk -> detect_object smallest at on the desk -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Leo", "in", "the", "study", "and", "tell", "the", "day", "of", "the", "week"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "O"], "slots": [{"intent": "meet", "person": "Leo", "location": "study"}, {"intent": "tell", "content": "day"}], "plan": "navigate to study -> meet_person Leo at study -> tell day"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "the", "pose", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "laundry", "room", "to", "the", "person", "at", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "content": "pose", "person": "person", "location": "garden table"}], "plan": "navigate to garden table -> tell pose"}
{"tokens": ["escort", "the", "standing", "person", "from", "the", "closet", "to", "the", "terrace"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "escort", "filter": "standing", "person": "person", "location": "terrace"}], "plan": "navigate to terrace -> guide_person person to terrace"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "largest", "object", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "largest", "location": "on the side table"}], "plan": "navigate to on the side table -> detect_object largest at on the side table -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "what", "day", "is", "today", "to", "the", "waving", "person", "in", "the", "office"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "I-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "content": "day today", "filter": "waving", "person": "person", "location": "office"}], "plan": "navigate to office -> tell day today"}
{"tokens": ["fetch", "a", "tray", "from", "the", "shelf", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "fetch", "object": "tray", "location": "shelf"}, {"intent": "deliver", "recipient": "me"}], "plan": "navigate to shelf -> detect_object tray at shelf -> deliver tray to me"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "remote", "there", "are", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "remote", "location": "on the shelf"}], "plan": "navigate to on the shelf -> count remote at on the shelf -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "drinks", "bar", "then", "meet", "Grace", "and", "say", "something", "about", "yourself"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-CONTENT"], "slots": [{"intent": "go", "location": "drinks bar"}, {"intent": "meet", "person": "Grace"}, {"intent": "say", "content": "yourself"}], "plan": "navigate to drinks bar -> meet_person Grace -> greet_person"}
{"tokens": ["introduce", "yourself", "to", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "red", "t", "shirt", "in", "the", "dining", "area", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"], "slots": [{"intent": "introduce", "person": "red t shirt", "filter": "wearing", "location": "dining area"}, {"intent": "follow"}], "plan": "navigate to dining area -> introduce_person -> guide_person"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "the", "gesture", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "laundry", "room", "to", "the", "person", "at", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "content": "gesture", "person": "person", "location": "counter"}], "plan": "navigate to counter -> tell gesture"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "the", "name", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "closet"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "person", "content": "name", "location": "closet"}], "plan": "navigate to closet -> tell name"}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Frank", "in", "the", "bedroom", "and", "take", "them", "to", "the", "balcony"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "meet", "person": "Frank", "location": "bedroom"}, {"intent": "take", "location": "balcony"}], "plan": "navigate to bedroom -> meet_person Frank at bedroom -> navigate to balcony -> grasp"}
{"tokens": ["follow", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "right", "arm", "at", "the", "garage"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "follow", "person": "person", "filter": "right arm", "location": "garage"}], "plan": "navigate to garage -> guide_person person to garage"}
{"tokens": ["guide", "Noah", "from", "the", "entrance", "to", "the", "bedroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "guide", "person": "Noah", "location": "bedroom"}], "plan": "navigate to bedroom -> guide_person Noah to bedroom"}
{"tokens": ["follow", "Rosa", "from", "the", "drinks", "bar", "to", "the", "terrace"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "follow", "person": "Rosa", "location": "terrace"}], "plan": "navigate to terrace -> guide_person Rosa to terrace"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "the", "pose", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "garden", "to", "the", "person", "at", "the", "laundry", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "content": "pose", "person": "person", "location": "laundry room"}], "plan": "navigate to laundry room -> tell pose"}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "mug", "in", "the", "laundry", "room", "then", "grasp", "it", "and", "place", "it", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "locate", "object": "mug", "location": "laundry room"}, {"intent": "grasp"}, {"intent": "place", "location": "on the counter"}], "plan": "navigate to laundry room -> detect_object mug at laundry room -> grasp -> navigate to on the counter -> place at on the counter"}
{"tokens": ["take", "Maria", "from", "the", "shelf", "to", "the", "bathroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "take", "person": "Maria", "location": "bathroom"}], "plan": "navigate to bathroom -> grasp"}
{"tokens": ["escort", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "white", "coat", "from", "the", "patio", "to", "the", "storage", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "escort", "person": "white coat", "filter": "wearing", "location": "storage room"}], "plan": "navigate to storage room -> guide_person white coat to storage room"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "cups", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "biggest", "object": "cups", "location": "on the shelf"}], "plan": "navigate to on the shelf -> detect_object biggest cups at on the shelf -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "smallest", "object", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "smallest", "location": "on the desk"}], "plan": "navigate to on the desk -> detect_object smallest at on the desk -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["give", "me", "a", "magazine", "from", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "give", "recipient": "me", "object": "magazine", "location": "side table"}], "plan": "navigate to side table -> grasp -> navigate to side table -> deliver magazine to me"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "object", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "biggest", "location": "on the desk"}], "plan": "navigate to on the desk -> detect_object biggest at on the desk -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "heaviest", "cans", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "heaviest", "object": "cans", "location": "on the side table"}], "plan": "navigate to on the side table -> detect_object heaviest cans at on the side table -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["grasp", "a", "cans", "from", "the", "shelf", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "the", "lying", "person", "in", "the", "workshop"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "grasp", "object": "cans", "location": "shelf"}, {"intent": "deliver", "filter": "lying", "recipient": "person", "location": "workshop"}], "plan": "navigate to shelf -> grasp -> navigate to workshop -> deliver cans to person"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "largest", "object", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "largest", "location": "on the desk"}], "plan": "navigate to on the desk -> detect_object largest at on the desk -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["fetch", "a", "books", "from", "the", "shelf", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "Alice", "in", "the", "living", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "fetch", "object": "books", "location": "shelf"}, {"intent": "bring", "recipient": "Alice", "location": "living room"}], "plan": "navigate to shelf -> detect_object books at shelf -> navigate to living room -> deliver books to Alice"}
{"tokens": ["say", "the", "day", "of", "the", "week", "to", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "left", "arm", "in", "the", "bathroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "say", "content": "day", "person": "person", "filter": "left arm", "location": "bathroom"}], "plan": "navigate to bathroom -> greet_person person with left arm at bathroom"}
{"tokens": ["guide", "the", "lying", "person", "from", "the", "garden", "table", "to", "the", "living", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "guide", "filter": "lying", "person": "person", "location": "living room"}], "plan": "navigate to living room -> guide_person person to living room"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "lightest", "books", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "lightest", "object": "books", "location": "on the shelf"}], "plan": "navigate to on the shelf -> detect_object lightest books at on the shelf -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["follow", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "right", "arm", "in", "the", "dining", "area"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "follow", "person": "person", "filter": "right arm", "location": "dining area"}], "plan": "navigate to dining area -> guide_person person to dining area"}
{"tokens": ["look", "for", "a", "mugs", "in", "the", "entrance", "then", "get", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "the", "sitting", "person", "in", "the", "entrance"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "look", "object": "mugs", "location": "entrance"}, {"intent": "get"}, {"intent": "deliver", "filter": "sitting", "recipient": "person", "location": "entrance"}], "plan": "navigate to entrance -> detect_object mugs at entrance -> grasp -> navigate to entrance -> deliver mugs to person"}
{"tokens": ["look", "for", "a", "pen", "in", "the", "kitchen", "then", "get", "it", "and", "give", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "look", "object": "pen", "location": "kitchen"}, {"intent": "get"}, {"intent": "give", "recipient": "me"}], "plan": "navigate to kitchen -> detect_object pen at kitchen -> grasp -> deliver pen to me"}
{"tokens": ["get", "a", "magazines", "from", "the", "side", "table", "and", "give", "it", "to", "Charlie", "in", "the", "office"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "get", "object": "magazines", "location": "side table"}, {"intent": "give", "recipient": "Charlie", "location": "office"}], "plan": "navigate to side table -> grasp -> navigate to office -> deliver magazines to Charlie"}
{"tokens": ["answer", "the", "question", "of", "the", "waving", "person", "in", "the", "bathroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "answer", "content": "question", "filter": "waving", "person": "person", "location": "bathroom"}], "plan": "navigate to bathroom -> detect_person with pose waving at bathroom -> navigate to operator -> answer_question"}
{"tokens": ["follow", "the", "lying", "person", "at", "the", "living", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "follow", "filter": "lying", "person": "person", "location": "living room"}], "plan": "navigate to living room -> guide_person person to living room"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "object", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "biggest", "location": "on the counter"}], "plan": "navigate to on the counter -> detect_object biggest at on the counter -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["say", "hello", "to", "Jack", "in", "the", "balcony", "and", "say", "your", "teams", "country"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "B-CONTENT", "I-CONTENT", "I-CONTENT"], "slots": [{"intent": "say", "person": "Jack", "location": "balcony"}, {"intent": "say", "content": "your teams country"}], "plan": "navigate to balcony -> greet_person Jack at balcony -> greet_person"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "dining", "area", "are", "wearing", "orange", "jackets"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "orange jackets", "location": "dining area", "filter": "wearing"}], "plan": "navigate to dining area -> detect_person with wearing at dining area -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["follow", "the", "sitting", "person", "in", "the", "terrace"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "follow", "filter": "sitting", "person": "person", "location": "terrace"}], "plan": "navigate to terrace -> guide_person person to terrace"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "the", "gesture", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "bedroom", "to", "the", "person", "at", "the", "living", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "content": "gesture", "person": "person", "location": "living room"}], "plan": "navigate to living room -> tell gesture"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "the", "name", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "garage", "to", "the", "person", "at", "the", "balcony"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "content": "name", "person": "person", "location": "balcony"}], "plan": "navigate to balcony -> tell name"}
{"tokens": ["answer", "the", "question", "of", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "right", "in", "the", "study"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "answer", "content": "question", "person": "person", "filter": "pointing", "location": "study"}], "plan": "navigate to study -> detect_person with pose pointing at study -> navigate to operator -> answer_question"}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "can", "in", "the", "study", "then", "grasp", "it", "and", "give", "it", "to", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "left", "in", "the", "study"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "locate", "object": "can", "location": "study"}, {"intent": "grasp"}, {"intent": "give", "recipient": "person", "filter": "pointing", "location": "study"}], "plan": "navigate to study -> detect_object can at study -> grasp -> navigate to study -> deliver can to person"}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "patio", "then", "find", "a", "charger", "and", "fetch", "it", "and", "give", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "navigate", "location": "patio"}, {"intent": "find", "object": "charger"}, {"intent": "fetch"}, {"intent": "give", "recipient": "me"}], "plan": "navigate to patio -> detect_object charger -> deliver charger to me"}
{"tokens": ["get", "a", "remotes", "from", "the", "garden", "table", "and", "give", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "get", "object": "remotes", "location": "garden table"}, {"intent": "give", "recipient": "me"}], "plan": "navigate to garden table -> grasp -> deliver remotes to me"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "book", "there", "are", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "book", "location": "on the side table"}], "plan": "navigate to on the side table -> count book at on the side table -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "the", "name", "of", "the", "person", "in", "the", "entrance"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "person", "content": "name", "location": "entrance"}], "plan": "navigate to entrance -> tell name"}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "right", "in", "the", "patio", "and", "lead", "them", "to", "the", "bedroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "find", "person": "person", "filter": "pointing", "location": "patio"}, {"intent": "lead", "location": "bedroom"}], "plan": "navigate to patio -> detect_person with pose pointing at patio -> navigate to bedroom -> guide_person to bedroom"}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "cans", "in", "the", "balcony", "then", "take", "it", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "find", "object": "cans", "location": "balcony"}, {"intent": "take"}, {"intent": "bring", "recipient": "me"}], "plan": "navigate to balcony -> detect_object cans at balcony -> grasp -> deliver cans to me"}
{"tokens": ["get", "a", "magazine", "from", "the", "shelf", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "Jack", "in", "the", "office"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "get", "object": "magazine", "location": "shelf"}, {"intent": "bring", "recipient": "Jack", "location": "office"}], "plan": "navigate to shelf -> grasp -> navigate to office -> deliver magazine to Jack"}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Frank", "at", "the", "drinks", "bar", "then", "find", "them", "in", "the", "living", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "meet", "person": "Frank", "location": "drinks bar"}, {"intent": "find", "location": "living room"}], "plan": "navigate to drinks bar -> meet_person Frank at drinks bar -> navigate to living room"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "heaviest", "magazines", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "heaviest", "object": "magazines", "location": "on the side table"}], "plan": "navigate to on the side table -> detect_object heaviest magazines at on the side table -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "entrance", "then", "locate", "the", "sitting", "person", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-VERB", "O"], "slots": [{"intent": "navigate", "location": "entrance"}, {"intent": "locate", "filter": "sitting", "person": "person"}, {"intent": "follow"}], "plan": "navigate to entrance -> detect_person with pose sitting -> guide_person"}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "sitting", "person", "in", "the", "garden", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"], "slots": [{"intent": "find", "filter": "sitting", "person": "person", "location": "garden"}, {"intent": "follow"}], "plan": "navigate to garden -> detect_person with pose sitting at garden -> guide_person"}
{"tokens": ["greet", "Diana", "in", "the", "kitchen", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"], "slots": [{"intent": "greet", "person": "Diana", "location": "kitchen"}, {"intent": "follow"}], "plan": "navigate to kitchen -> greet_person Diana at kitchen -> guide_person"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "can", "there", "are", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "can", "location": "on the counter"}], "plan": "navigate to on the counter -> count can at on the counter -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "standing", "person", "in", "the", "kitchen", "and", "say", "your", "teams", "name"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "B-CONTENT", "I-CONTENT", "I-CONTENT"], "slots": [{"intent": "find", "filter": "standing", "person": "person", "location": "kitchen"}, {"intent": "say", "content": "your teams name"}], "plan": "navigate to kitchen -> detect_person with pose standing at kitchen -> greet_person"}
{"tokens": ["bring", "me", "a", "glass", "from", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "bring", "recipient": "me", "object": "glass", "location": "garden table"}], "plan": "navigate to garden table -> grasp -> navigate to garden table -> deliver glass to me"}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "magazines", "in", "the", "bathroom", "then", "get", "it", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "locate", "object": "magazines", "location": "bathroom"}, {"intent": "get"}, {"intent": "bring", "recipient": "me"}], "plan": "navigate to bathroom -> detect_object magazines at bathroom -> grasp -> deliver magazines to me"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "heaviest", "magazines", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "heaviest", "object": "magazines", "location": "on the counter"}], "plan": "navigate to on the counter -> detect_object heaviest magazines at on the counter -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "smallest", "cans", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "smallest", "object": "cans", "location": "on the shelf"}], "plan": "navigate to on the shelf -> detect_object smallest cans at on the shelf -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "bottle", "there", "are", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "bottle", "location": "on the shelf"}], "plan": "navigate to on the shelf -> count bottle at on the shelf -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["follow", "Maria", "from", "the", "side", "table", "to", "the", "storage", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "follow", "person": "Maria", "location": "storage room"}], "plan": "navigate to storage room -> guide_person Maria to storage room"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "book", "there", "are", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "book", "location": "on the side table"}], "plan": "navigate to on the side table -> count book at on the side table -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "glass", "in", "the", "balcony", "then", "take", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "locate", "object": "glass", "location": "balcony"}, {"intent": "take"}, {"intent": "deliver", "recipient": "me"}], "plan": "navigate to balcony -> detect_object glass at balcony -> grasp -> deliver glass to me"}
{"tokens": ["get", "a", "tablet", "from", "the", "garden", "table", "and", "place", "it", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "get", "object": "tablet", "location": "garden table"}, {"intent": "place", "location": "on the side table"}], "plan": "navigate to garden table -> grasp -> navigate to on the side table -> place at on the side table"}
{"tokens": ["fetch", "a", "charger", "from", "the", "garden", "table", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "Leo", "in", "the", "terrace"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "fetch", "object": "charger", "location": "garden table"}, {"intent": "bring", "recipient": "Leo", "location": "terrace"}], "plan": "navigate to garden table -> detect_object charger at garden table -> navigate to terrace -> deliver charger to Leo"}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "bedroom", "then", "find", "a", "snacks", "and", "take", "it", "and", "put", "it", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "go", "location": "bedroom"}, {"intent": "find", "object": "snacks"}, {"intent": "take"}, {"intent": "put", "location": "on the counter"}], "plan": "navigate to bedroom -> detect_object snacks -> grasp -> navigate to on the counter -> place at on the counter"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "lying", "persons", "are", "in", "the", "storage", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "filter": "lying", "location": "storage room"}], "plan": "navigate to storage room -> detect_person with pose lying at storage room -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "drinks", "bar", "then", "meet", "Maria", "and", "lead", "them", "to", "the", "bathroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "navigate", "location": "drinks bar"}, {"intent": "meet", "person": "Maria"}, {"intent": "lead", "location": "bathroom"}], "plan": "navigate to drinks bar -> meet_person Maria -> navigate to bathroom -> guide_person to bathroom"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "what", "day", "is", "tomorrow", "to", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "right", "in", "the", "kitchen"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "I-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "content": "day tomorrow", "person": "person", "filter": "pointing", "location": "kitchen"}], "plan": "navigate to kitchen -> tell day tomorrow"}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "pen", "in", "the", "entrance", "then", "take", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "Ingrid", "in", "the", "entrance"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "find", "object": "pen", "location": "entrance"}, {"intent": "take"}, {"intent": "deliver", "recipient": "Ingrid", "location": "entrance"}], "plan": "navigate to entrance -> detect_object pen at entrance -> grasp -> navigate to entrance -> deliver pen to Ingrid"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "waving", "persons", "are", "in", "the", "hallway"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "filter": "waving", "location": "hallway"}], "plan": "navigate to hallway -> detect_person with pose waving at hallway -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "entrance", "are", "wearing", "black", "shirts"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "black shirts", "location": "entrance", "filter": "wearing"}], "plan": "navigate to entrance -> detect_person with wearing at entrance -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "hallway", "are", "wearing", "white", "sweaters"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "white sweaters", "location": "hallway", "filter": "wearing"}], "plan": "navigate to hallway -> detect_person with wearing at hallway -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "tablet", "in", "the", "study", "then", "fetch", "it", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "the", "sitting", "person", "in", "the", "study"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "find", "object": "tablet", "location": "study"}, {"intent": "fetch"}, {"intent": "bring", "filter": "sitting", "recipient": "person", "location": "study"}], "plan": "navigate to study -> detect_object tablet at study -> navigate to study -> deliver tablet to person"}
{"tokens": ["give", "me", "a", "book", "from", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "give", "recipient": "me", "object": "book", "location": "shelf"}], "plan": "navigate to shelf -> grasp -> navigate to shelf -> deliver book to me"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "remote", "there", "are", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "remote", "location": "on the garden table"}], "plan": "navigate to on the garden table -> count remote at on the garden table -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "the", "pose", "of", "the", "person", "in", "the", "laundry", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "person", "content": "pose", "location": "laundry room"}], "plan": "navigate to laundry room -> tell pose"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "lightest", "mugs", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "lightest", "object": "mugs", "location": "on the counter"}], "plan": "navigate to on the counter -> detect_object lightest mugs at on the counter -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["look", "for", "a", "bottles", "in", "the", "storage", "room", "then", "fetch", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "left", "in", "the", "storage", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "look", "object": "bottles", "location": "storage room"}, {"intent": "fetch"}, {"intent": "deliver", "recipient": "person", "filter": "pointing", "location": "storage room"}], "plan": "navigate to storage room -> detect_object bottles at storage room -> navigate to storage room -> deliver bottles to person"}
{"tokens": ["follow", "Charlie", "from", "the", "office", "to", "the", "workshop"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "follow", "person": "Charlie", "location": "workshop"}], "plan": "navigate to workshop -> guide_person Charlie to workshop"}
{"tokens": ["follow", "the", "sitting", "person", "in", "the", "study"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "follow", "filter": "sitting", "person": "person", "location": "study"}], "plan": "navigate to study -> guide_person person to study"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "toy", "there", "are", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "toy", "location": "on the desk"}], "plan": "navigate to on the desk -> count toy at on the desk -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["introduce", "yourself", "to", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "yellow", "t", "shirt", "in", "the", "terrace", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"], "slots": [{"intent": "introduce", "person": "yellow t shirt", "filter": "wearing", "location": "terrace"}, {"intent": "follow"}], "plan": "navigate to terrace -> introduce_person -> guide_person"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "the", "name", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "kitchen", "to", "the", "person", "at", "the", "terrace"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "content": "name", "person": "person", "location": "terrace"}], "plan": "navigate to terrace -> tell name"}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Bob", "at", "the", "bedroom", "then", "locate", "them", "in", "the", "garden"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "meet", "person": "Bob", "location": "bedroom"}, {"intent": "locate", "location": "garden"}], "plan": "navigate to bedroom -> meet_person Bob at bedroom -> navigate to garden"}
{"tokens": ["say", "something", "about", "yourself", "to", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "right", "in", "the", "laundry", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "say", "content": "yourself", "person": "person", "filter": "pointing", "location": "laundry room"}], "plan": "navigate to laundry room -> greet_person person with pointing at laundry room"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "living", "room", "are", "wearing", "yellow", "shirts"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "yellow shirts", "location": "living room", "filter": "wearing"}], "plan": "navigate to living room -> detect_person with wearing at living room -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "lightest", "mugs", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "lightest", "object": "mugs", "location": "on the shelf"}], "plan": "navigate to on the shelf -> detect_object lightest mugs at on the shelf -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "the", "name", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "workshop", "to", "the", "person", "at", "the", "bedroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "content": "name", "person": "person", "location": "bedroom"}], "plan": "navigate to bedroom -> tell name"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "hallway", "are", "wearing", "yellow", "shirts"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "yellow shirts", "location": "hallway", "filter": "wearing"}], "plan": "navigate to hallway -> detect_person with wearing at hallway -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "magazine", "there", "are", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "magazine", "location": "on the side table"}], "plan": "navigate to on the side table -> count magazine at on the side table -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "toys", "in", "the", "bathroom", "then", "grasp", "it", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "locate", "object": "toys", "location": "bathroom"}, {"intent": "grasp"}, {"intent": "bring", "recipient": "me"}], "plan": "navigate to bathroom -> detect_object toys at bathroom -> grasp -> deliver toys to me"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "the", "pose", "of", "the", "person", "in", "the", "drinks", "bar"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "person", "content": "pose", "location": "drinks bar"}], "plan": "navigate to drinks bar -> tell pose"}
{"tokens": ["bring", "me", "a", "tray", "from", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "bring", "recipient": "me", "object": "tray", "location": "side table"}], "plan": "navigate to side table -> grasp -> navigate to side table -> deliver tray to me"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "glass", "there", "are", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "glass", "location": "on the counter"}], "plan": "navigate to on the counter -> count glass at on the counter -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Jack", "in", "the", "drinks", "bar", "and", "escort", "them", "to", "the", "hallway"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "meet", "person": "Jack", "location": "drinks bar"}, {"intent": "escort", "location": "hallway"}], "plan": "navigate to drinks bar -> meet_person Jack at drinks bar -> navigate to hallway -> guide_person to hallway"}
{"tokens": ["bring", "me", "a", "snack", "from", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "bring", "recipient": "me", "object": "snack", "location": "counter"}], "plan": "navigate to counter -> grasp -> navigate to counter -> deliver snack to me"}
{"tokens": ["answer", "the", "quiz", "of", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "left", "arm", "in", "the", "dining", "area"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "answer", "content": "quiz", "person": "person", "filter": "left arm", "location": "dining area"}], "plan": "navigate to dining area -> detect_person with left arm at dining area -> navigate to operator -> answer_question"}
{"tokens": ["answer", "the", "question", "of", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "left", "arm", "in", "the", "patio"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "answer", "content": "question", "person": "person", "filter": "left arm", "location": "patio"}], "plan": "navigate to patio -> detect_person with left arm at patio -> navigate to operator -> answer_question"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "the", "pose", "of", "the", "person", "in", "the", "living", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "person", "content": "pose", "location": "living room"}], "plan": "navigate to living room -> tell pose"}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "workshop", "then", "look", "for", "a", "plates", "and", "get", "it", "and", "give", "it", "to", "Tom", "in", "the", "patio"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "navigate", "location": "workshop"}, {"intent": "look", "object": "plates"}, {"intent": "get"}, {"intent": "give", "recipient": "Tom", "location": "patio"}], "plan": "navigate to workshop -> detect_object plates -> grasp -> navigate to patio -> deliver plates to Tom"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "lightest", "cups", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "lightest", "object": "cups", "location": "on the side table"}], "plan": "navigate to on the side table -> detect_object lightest cups at on the side table -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["get", "a", "bowl", "from", "the", "garden", "table", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "get", "object": "bowl", "location": "garden table"}, {"intent": "deliver", "recipient": "me"}], "plan": "navigate to garden table -> grasp -> deliver bowl to me"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "kitchen", "are", "wearing", "red", "sweaters"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "red sweaters", "location": "kitchen", "filter": "wearing"}], "plan": "navigate to kitchen -> detect_person with wearing at kitchen -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["get", "a", "magazines", "from", "the", "shelf", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "get", "object": "magazines", "location": "shelf"}, {"intent": "deliver", "recipient": "me"}], "plan": "navigate to shelf -> grasp -> deliver magazines to me"}
{"tokens": ["take", "Karen", "from", "the", "hallway", "to", "the", "entrance"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "take", "person": "Karen", "location": "entrance"}], "plan": "navigate to entrance -> grasp"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "waving", "persons", "are", "in", "the", "hallway"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "filter": "waving", "location": "hallway"}], "plan": "navigate to hallway -> detect_person with pose waving at hallway -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "persons", "pointing", "to", "the", "left", "are", "in", "the", "kitchen"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "filter": "pointing", "location": "kitchen"}], "plan": "navigate to kitchen -> detect_person with pose pointing at kitchen -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "magazines", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "biggest", "object": "magazines", "location": "on the side table"}], "plan": "navigate to on the side table -> detect_object biggest magazines at on the side table -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Ingrid", "in", "the", "dining", "area", "and", "escort", "them", "to", "the", "bedroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "meet", "person": "Ingrid", "location": "dining area"}, {"intent": "escort", "location": "bedroom"}], "plan": "navigate to dining area -> meet_person Ingrid at dining area -> navigate to bedroom -> guide_person to bedroom"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "heaviest", "remotes", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "heaviest", "object": "remotes", "location": "on the counter"}], "plan": "navigate to on the counter -> detect_object heaviest remotes at on the counter -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "remote", "there", "are", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "remote", "location": "on the shelf"}], "plan": "navigate to on the shelf -> count remote at on the shelf -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "can", "there", "are", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "can", "location": "on the shelf"}], "plan": "navigate to on the shelf -> count can at on the shelf -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["guide", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "right", "from", "the", "garden", "to", "the", "patio"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "guide", "person": "person", "filter": "pointing", "location": "patio"}], "plan": "navigate to patio -> guide_person person to patio"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "smallest", "remotes", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "smallest", "object": "remotes", "location": "on the side table"}], "plan": "navigate to on the side table -> detect_object smallest remotes at on the side table -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "thinnest", "object", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "thinnest", "location": "on the counter"}], "plan": "navigate to on the counter -> detect_object thinnest at on the counter -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "heaviest", "object", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "heaviest", "location": "on the side table"}], "plan": "navigate to on the side table -> detect_object heaviest at on the side table -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["answer", "the", "quiz", "of", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "right", "arm", "in", "the", "patio"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "answer", "content": "quiz", "person": "person", "filter": "right arm", "location": "patio"}], "plan": "navigate to patio -> detect_person with right arm at patio -> navigate to operator -> answer_question"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "thinnest", "object", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "thinnest", "location": "on the counter"}], "plan": "navigate to on the counter -> detect_object thinnest at on the counter -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["say", "hello", "to", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "white", "coat", "in", "the", "entrance", "and", "answer", "a", "quiz"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT"], "slots": [{"intent": "say", "person": "white coat", "filter": "wearing", "location": "entrance"}, {"intent": "answer", "content": "quiz"}], "plan": "navigate to entrance -> greet_person white coat with wearing at entrance -> navigate to operator -> answer_question"}
{"tokens": ["introduce", "yourself", "to", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "white", "coat", "in", "the", "terrace", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"], "slots": [{"intent": "introduce", "person": "white coat", "filter": "wearing", "location": "terrace"}, {"intent": "follow"}], "plan": "navigate to terrace -> introduce_person -> guide_person"}
{"tokens": ["look", "for", "a", "charger", "in", "the", "kitchen", "then", "grasp", "it", "and", "give", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "look", "object": "charger", "location": "kitchen"}, {"intent": "grasp"}, {"intent": "give", "recipient": "me"}], "plan": "navigate to kitchen -> detect_object charger at kitchen -> grasp -> deliver charger to me"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "lightest", "object", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "lightest", "location": "on the desk"}], "plan": "navigate to on the desk -> detect_object lightest at on the desk -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["look", "for", "a", "lying", "person", "in", "the", "office", "and", "answer", "a", "quiz"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT"], "slots": [{"intent": "look", "filter": "lying", "person": "person", "location": "office"}, {"intent": "answer", "content": "quiz"}], "plan": "navigate to office -> detect_person with pose lying at office -> navigate to operator -> answer_question"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "heaviest", "object", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "heaviest", "location": "on the counter"}], "plan": "navigate to on the counter -> detect_object heaviest at on the counter -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "office", "then", "locate", "a", "glasses", "and", "grasp", "it", "and", "give", "it", "to", "Rosa", "in", "the", "study"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "navigate", "location": "office"}, {"intent": "locate", "object": "glasses"}, {"intent": "grasp"}, {"intent": "give", "recipient": "Rosa", "location": "study"}], "plan": "navigate to office -> detect_object glasses -> grasp -> navigate to study -> deliver glasses to Rosa"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "bottle", "there", "are", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "bottle", "location": "on the shelf"}], "plan": "navigate to on the shelf -> count bottle at on the shelf -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "the", "gesture", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "person", "content": "gesture", "location": "side table"}], "plan": "navigate to side table -> tell gesture"}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Noah", "in", "the", "hallway", "and", "follow", "them", "to", "the", "terrace"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "meet", "person": "Noah", "location": "hallway"}, {"intent": "follow", "location": "terrace"}], "plan": "navigate to hallway -> meet_person Noah at hallway -> navigate to terrace -> guide_person to terrace"}
{"tokens": ["answer", "the", "quiz", "of", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "right", "in", "the", "balcony"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "answer", "content": "quiz", "person": "person", "filter": "pointing", "location": "balcony"}], "plan": "navigate to balcony -> detect_person with pose pointing at balcony -> navigate to operator -> answer_question"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "largest", "object", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "largest", "location": "on the shelf"}], "plan": "navigate to on the shelf -> detect_object largest at on the shelf -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "kitchen", "are", "wearing", "black", "shirts"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "black shirts", "location": "kitchen", "filter": "wearing"}], "plan": "navigate to kitchen -> detect_person with wearing at kitchen -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "study", "are", "wearing", "white", "t", "shirts"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "white t shirts", "location": "study", "filter": "wearing"}], "plan": "navigate to study -> detect_person with wearing at study -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "cup", "there", "are", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "cup", "location": "on the side table"}], "plan": "navigate to on the side table -> count cup at on the side table -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Rosa", "at", "the", "study", "then", "look", "for", "them", "in", "the", "office"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "meet", "person": "Rosa", "location": "study"}, {"intent": "look", "location": "office"}], "plan": "navigate to study -> meet_person Rosa at study -> navigate to office"}
{"tokens": ["say", "your", "teams", "affiliation", "to", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "right", "in", "the", "laundry", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "say", "person": "person", "filter": "pointing", "location": "laundry room"}], "plan": "navigate to laundry room -> greet_person person with pointing at laundry room"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "magazine", "there", "are", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "magazine", "location": "on the shelf"}], "plan": "navigate to on the shelf -> count magazine at on the shelf -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "smallest", "object", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "smallest", "location": "on the side table"}], "plan": "navigate to on the side table -> detect_object smallest at on the side table -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "heaviest", "object", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "heaviest", "location": "on the shelf"}], "plan": "navigate to on the shelf -> detect_object heaviest at on the shelf -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["follow", "Alice", "from", "the", "counter", "to", "the", "drinks", "bar"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "follow", "person": "Alice", "location": "drinks bar"}], "plan": "navigate to drinks bar -> guide_person Alice to drinks bar"}
{"tokens": ["escort", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "gray", "coat", "from", "the", "balcony", "to", "the", "closet"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "escort", "person": "gray coat", "filter": "wearing", "location": "closet"}], "plan": "navigate to closet -> guide_person gray coat to closet"}
{"tokens": ["get", "a", "toys", "from", "the", "shelf", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "the", "waving", "person", "in", "the", "closet"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "get", "object": "toys", "location": "shelf"}, {"intent": "bring", "filter": "waving", "recipient": "person", "location": "closet"}], "plan": "navigate to shelf -> grasp -> navigate to closet -> deliver toys to person"}
{"tokens": ["guide", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "black", "sweater", "from", "the", "kitchen", "to", "the", "laundry", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "guide", "person": "black sweater", "filter": "wearing", "location": "laundry room"}], "plan": "navigate to laundry room -> guide_person black sweater to laundry room"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "what", "day", "is", "today", "to", "the", "waving", "person", "in", "the", "hallway"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "I-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "content": "day today", "filter": "waving", "person": "person", "location": "hallway"}], "plan": "navigate to hallway -> tell day today"}
{"tokens": ["follow", "the", "standing", "person", "at", "the", "workshop"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "follow", "filter": "standing", "person": "person", "location": "workshop"}], "plan": "navigate to workshop -> guide_person person to workshop"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "the", "time", "to", "the", "waving", "person", "in", "the", "bedroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "content": "time", "filter": "waving", "person": "person", "location": "bedroom"}], "plan": "navigate to bedroom -> tell time"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "closet", "are", "wearing", "yellow", "blouses"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "yellow blouses", "location": "closet", "filter": "wearing"}], "plan": "navigate to closet -> detect_person with wearing at closet -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["say", "hello", "to", "Grace", "in", "the", "hallway", "and", "escort", "them", "to", "the", "patio"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "say", "person": "Grace", "location": "hallway"}, {"intent": "escort", "location": "patio"}], "plan": "navigate to hallway -> greet_person Grace at hallway -> navigate to patio -> guide_person to patio"}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "sitting", "person", "in", "the", "hallway", "and", "follow", "them", "to", "the", "patio"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "find", "filter": "sitting", "person": "person", "location": "hallway"}, {"intent": "follow", "location": "patio"}], "plan": "navigate to hallway -> detect_person with pose sitting at hallway -> navigate to patio -> guide_person to patio"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "object", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "biggest", "location": "on the desk"}], "plan": "navigate to on the desk -> detect_object biggest at on the desk -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Alice", "at", "the", "workshop", "then", "look", "for", "them", "in", "the", "terrace"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "meet", "person": "Alice", "location": "workshop"}, {"intent": "look", "location": "terrace"}], "plan": "navigate to workshop -> meet_person Alice at workshop -> navigate to terrace"}
{"tokens": ["guide", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "blue", "shirt", "from", "the", "counter", "to", "the", "drinks", "bar"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "guide", "person": "blue shirt", "filter": "wearing", "location": "drinks bar"}], "plan": "navigate to drinks bar -> guide_person blue shirt to drinks bar"}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "laundry", "room", "then", "locate", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "left", "and", "follow", "them", "to", "the", "drinks", "bar"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "navigate", "location": "laundry room"}, {"intent": "locate", "person": "person", "filter": "pointing", "location": "left"}, {"intent": "follow", "location": "drinks bar"}], "plan": "navigate to laundry room -> navigate to left -> detect_person with pose pointing at left -> navigate to drinks bar -> guide_person to drinks bar"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "largest", "object", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "largest", "location": "on the shelf"}], "plan": "navigate to on the shelf -> detect_object largest at on the shelf -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["look", "for", "a", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "left", "in", "the", "garage", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"], "slots": [{"intent": "look", "person": "person", "filter": "pointing", "location": "garage"}, {"intent": "follow"}], "plan": "navigate to garage -> detect_person with pose pointing at garage -> guide_person"}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "patio", "then", "look", "for", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "left", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"], "slots": [{"intent": "go", "location": "patio"}, {"intent": "look", "person": "person", "filter": "pointing", "location": "left"}, {"intent": "follow"}], "plan": "navigate to patio -> navigate to left -> detect_person with pose pointing at left -> guide_person"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "workshop", "are", "wearing", "red", "t", "shirts"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "red t shirts", "location": "workshop", "filter": "wearing"}], "plan": "navigate to workshop -> detect_person with wearing at workshop -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Eva", "in", "the", "terrace", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"], "slots": [{"intent": "meet", "person": "Eva", "location": "terrace"}, {"intent": "follow"}], "plan": "navigate to terrace -> meet_person Eva at terrace -> guide_person"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "the", "pose", "of", "the", "person", "in", "the", "storage", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "person", "content": "pose", "location": "storage room"}], "plan": "navigate to storage room -> tell pose"}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "balcony", "then", "look", "for", "a", "snack", "and", "grasp", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "navigate", "location": "balcony"}, {"intent": "look", "object": "snack"}, {"intent": "grasp"}, {"intent": "deliver", "recipient": "me"}], "plan": "navigate to balcony -> detect_object snack -> grasp -> deliver snack to me"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "mug", "there", "are", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "mug", "location": "on the side table"}], "plan": "navigate to on the side table -> count mug at on the side table -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "terrace", "then", "look", "for", "a", "charger", "and", "take", "it", "and", "give", "it", "to", "Bob", "in", "the", "garage"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "go", "location": "terrace"}, {"intent": "look", "object": "charger"}, {"intent": "take"}, {"intent": "give", "recipient": "Bob", "location": "garage"}], "plan": "navigate to terrace -> detect_object charger -> grasp -> navigate to garage -> deliver charger to Bob"}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Charlie", "in", "the", "garden", "and", "tell", "what", "day", "is", "tomorrow"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "I-CONTENT"], "slots": [{"intent": "meet", "person": "Charlie", "location": "garden"}, {"intent": "tell", "content": "day tomorrow"}], "plan": "navigate to garden -> meet_person Charlie at garden -> tell day tomorrow"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "lightest", "object", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "lightest", "location": "on the side table"}], "plan": "navigate to on the side table -> detect_object lightest at on the side table -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "book", "there", "are", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "book", "location": "on the desk"}], "plan": "navigate to on the desk -> count book at on the desk -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "bedroom", "are", "wearing", "red", "coats"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "red coats", "location": "bedroom", "filter": "wearing"}], "plan": "navigate to bedroom -> detect_person with wearing at bedroom -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["greet", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "black", "coat", "in", "the", "workshop", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"], "slots": [{"intent": "greet", "person": "black coat", "filter": "wearing", "location": "workshop"}, {"intent": "follow"}], "plan": "navigate to workshop -> greet_person black coat with wearing at workshop -> guide_person"}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "cans", "in", "the", "office", "then", "take", "it", "and", "place", "it", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "locate", "object": "cans", "location": "office"}, {"intent": "take"}, {"intent": "place", "location": "on the desk"}], "plan": "navigate to office -> detect_object cans at office -> grasp -> navigate to on the desk -> place at on the desk"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "mugs", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "biggest", "object": "mugs", "location": "on the garden table"}], "plan": "navigate to on the garden table -> detect_object biggest mugs at on the garden table -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["guide", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "right", "arm", "from", "the", "garden", "table", "to", "the", "living", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "guide", "person": "person", "filter": "right arm", "location": "living room"}], "plan": "navigate to living room -> guide_person person to living room"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "can", "there", "are", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "can", "location": "on the side table"}], "plan": "navigate to on the side table -> count can at on the side table -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "object", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "biggest", "location": "on the garden table"}], "plan": "navigate to on the garden table -> detect_object biggest at on the garden table -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["look", "for", "a", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "left", "in", "the", "hallway", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"], "slots": [{"intent": "look", "person": "person", "filter": "pointing", "location": "hallway"}, {"intent": "follow"}], "plan": "navigate to hallway -> detect_person with pose pointing at hallway -> guide_person"}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "workshop", "then", "find", "a", "bottles", "and", "grasp", "it", "and", "put", "it", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "navigate", "location": "workshop"}, {"intent": "find", "object": "bottles"}, {"intent": "grasp"}, {"intent": "put", "location": "on the desk"}], "plan": "navigate to workshop -> detect_object bottles -> grasp -> navigate to on the desk -> place at on the desk"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "thinnest", "mugs", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "thinnest", "object": "mugs", "location": "on the shelf"}], "plan": "navigate to on the shelf -> detect_object thinnest mugs at on the shelf -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "entrance", "then", "find", "a", "charger", "and", "get", "it", "and", "give", "it", "to", "Alice", "in", "the", "balcony"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "go", "location": "entrance"}, {"intent": "find", "object": "charger"}, {"intent": "get"}, {"intent": "give", "recipient": "Alice", "location": "balcony"}], "plan": "navigate to entrance -> detect_object charger -> grasp -> navigate to balcony -> deliver charger to Alice"}
{"tokens": ["take", "a", "pen", "from", "the", "garden", "table", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "the", "standing", "person", "in", "the", "garage"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "take", "object": "pen", "location": "garden table"}, {"intent": "deliver", "filter": "standing", "recipient": "person", "location": "garage"}], "plan": "navigate to garden table -> grasp -> navigate to garage -> deliver pen to person"}
{"tokens": ["guide", "Hector", "from", "the", "dining", "area", "to", "the", "drinks", "bar"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "guide", "person": "Hector", "location": "drinks bar"}], "plan": "navigate to drinks bar -> guide_person Hector to drinks bar"}
{"tokens": ["look", "for", "a", "standing", "person", "in", "the", "bathroom", "and", "lead", "them", "to", "the", "office"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "look", "filter": "standing", "person": "person", "location": "bathroom"}, {"intent": "lead", "location": "office"}], "plan": "navigate to bathroom -> detect_person with pose standing at bathroom -> navigate to office -> guide_person to office"}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "standing", "person", "in", "the", "dining", "area", "and", "tell", "something", "about", "yourself"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-CONTENT"], "slots": [{"intent": "find", "filter": "standing", "person": "person", "location": "dining area"}, {"intent": "tell", "content": "yourself"}], "plan": "navigate to dining area -> detect_person with pose standing at dining area -> tell yourself"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "hallway", "are", "wearing", "red", "coats"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "red coats", "location": "hallway", "filter": "wearing"}], "plan": "navigate to hallway -> detect_person with wearing at hallway -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Tom", "in", "the", "patio", "and", "answer", "a", "question"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT"], "slots": [{"intent": "meet", "person": "Tom", "location": "patio"}, {"intent": "answer", "content": "question"}], "plan": "navigate to patio -> meet_person Tom at patio -> navigate to operator -> answer_question"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "thinnest", "bottles", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "thinnest", "object": "bottles", "location": "on the desk"}], "plan": "navigate to on the desk -> detect_object thinnest bottles at on the desk -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "lightest", "object", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "lightest", "location": "on the garden table"}], "plan": "navigate to on the garden table -> detect_object lightest at on the garden table -> describe_property -> navigate to operator -> tell"}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "terrace", "then", "locate", "a", "snacks", "and", "take", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "right", "arm", "in", "the", "kitchen"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "go", "location": "terrace"}, {"intent": "locate", "object": "snacks"}, {"intent": "take"}, {"intent": "deliver", "recipient": "person", "filter": "right arm", "location": "kitchen"}], "plan": "navigate to terrace -> detect_object snacks -> grasp -> navigate to kitchen -> deliver snacks to person"}
