{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "toys", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "biggest", "object": "toys", "location": "on the side table"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "heaviest", "toys", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "heaviest", "object": "toys", "location": "on the desk"}]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "bathroom", "then", "locate", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "right", "arm", "and", "guide", "them", "to", "the", "drinks", "bar"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "navigate", "location": "bathroom"}, {"intent": "locate", "person": "person", "filter": "right arm"}, {"intent": "guide", "location": "drinks bar"}]}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "cans", "in", "the", "bedroom", "then", "get", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "left", "arm", "in", "the", "bedroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "locate", "object": "cans", "location": "bedroom"}, {"intent": "get"}, {"intent": "deliver", "recipient": "person", "filter": "left arm", "location": "bedroom"}]}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "book", "in", "the", "living", "room", "then", "grasp", "it", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "locate", "object": "book", "location": "living room"}, {"intent": "grasp"}, {"intent": "bring", "recipient": "me"}]}
{"tokens": ["greet", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "yellow", "t", "shirt", "in", "the", "terrace", "and", "guide", "them", "to", "the", "bedroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "greet", "person": "yellow t shirt", "filter": "wearing", "location": "terrace"}, {"intent": "guide", "location": "bedroom"}]}
{"tokens": ["lead", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "orange", "jacket", "from", "the", "workshop", "to", "the", "workshop"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "lead", "person": "orange jacket", "filter": "wearing", "location": "workshop"}]}
{"tokens": ["bring", "me", "a", "tablet", "from", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "bring", "recipient": "me", "object": "tablet", "location": "shelf"}]}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "study", "then", "meet", "Rosa", "and", "say", "your", "teams", "name"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-VERB", "B-CONTENT", "I-CONTENT", "I-CONTENT"], "slots": [{"intent": "go", "location": "study"}, {"intent": "meet", "person": "Rosa"}, {"intent": "say", "content": "your teams name"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "plate", "there", "are", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "plate", "location": "on the counter"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "thinnest", "object", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "thinnest", "location": "on the shelf"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "lightest", "object", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "lightest", "location": "on the shelf"}]}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "standing", "person", "in", "the", "closet", "and", "escort", "them", "to", "the", "workshop"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "find", "filter": "standing", "person": "person", "location": "closet"}, {"intent": "escort", "location": "workshop"}]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "desk", "then", "locate", "a", "cans", "and", "get", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "Karen", "in", "the", "storage", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "navigate", "location": "desk"}, {"intent": "locate", "object": "cans"}, {"intent": "get"}, {"intent": "deliver", "recipient": "Karen", "location": "storage room"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "smallest", "object", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "smallest", "location": "on the desk"}]}
{"tokens": ["salute", "the", "person", "wearing", "an", "orange", "t", "shirt", "in", "the", "laundry", "room", "and", "tell", "the", "time"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT"], "slots": [{"intent": "salute", "person": "orange t shirt", "filter": "wearing", "location": "laundry room"}, {"intent": "tell", "content": "time"}]}
{"tokens": ["get", "a", "remotes", "from", "the", "desk", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "get", "object": "remotes", "location": "desk"}, {"intent": "bring", "recipient": "me"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "the", "pose", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "garden", "table", "to", "the", "person", "at", "the", "bathroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "content": "pose", "person": "person", "location": "bathroom"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "bottle", "there", "are", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "bottle", "location": "on the desk"}]}
{"tokens": ["grasp", "a", "plates", "from", "the", "desk", "and", "place", "it", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "grasp", "object": "plates", "location": "desk"}, {"intent": "place", "location": "on the counter"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "cup", "there", "are", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "cup", "location": "on the garden table"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "closet", "are", "wearing", "blue", "shirts"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "blue shirts", "location": "closet", "filter": "wearing"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "glass", "there", "are", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "glass", "location": "on the garden table"}]}
{"tokens": ["escort", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "gray", "t", "shirt", "from", "the", "garage", "to", "the", "office"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "escort", "person": "gray t shirt", "filter": "wearing", "location": "office"}]}
{"tokens": ["escort", "Sam", "from", "the", "garden", "to", "the", "laundry", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "escort", "person": "Sam", "location": "laundry room"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "object", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "biggest", "location": "on the counter"}]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Tom", "in", "the", "workshop", "and", "follow", "them", "to", "the", "office"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "meet", "person": "Tom", "location": "workshop"}, {"intent": "follow", "location": "office"}]}
{"tokens": ["bring", "me", "a", "plate", "from", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "bring", "recipient": "me", "object": "plate", "location": "side table"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "workshop", "are", "wearing", "orange", "coats"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "orange coats", "location": "workshop", "filter": "wearing"}]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "study", "then", "find", "a", "box", "and", "grasp", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "Rosa", "in", "the", "workshop"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "navigate", "location": "study"}, {"intent": "find", "object": "box"}, {"intent": "grasp"}, {"intent": "deliver", "recipient": "Rosa", "location": "workshop"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "largest", "bottles", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "largest", "object": "bottles", "location": "on the garden table"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "can", "there", "are", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "can", "location": "on the side table"}]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "Olivia", "from", "the", "terrace", "to", "the", "garden"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "follow", "person": "Olivia", "location": "garden"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "thinnest", "mugs", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "thinnest", "object": "mugs", "location": "on the counter"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "lightest", "object", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "lightest", "location": "on the counter"}]}
{"tokens": ["take", "a", "bottles", "from", "the", "shelf", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "take", "object": "bottles", "location": "shelf"}, {"intent": "bring", "recipient": "me"}]}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "toy", "in", "the", "study", "then", "get", "it", "and", "place", "it", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "locate", "object": "toy", "location": "study"}, {"intent": "get"}, {"intent": "place", "location": "on the garden table"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "entrance", "are", "wearing", "white", "jackets"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "white jackets", "location": "entrance", "filter": "wearing"}]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Ingrid", "at", "the", "study", "then", "find", "them", "in", "the", "closet"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "meet", "person": "Ingrid", "location": "study"}, {"intent": "find", "location": "closet"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "kitchen", "are", "wearing", "white", "t", "shirts"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "white t shirts", "location": "kitchen", "filter": "wearing"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "smallest", "object", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "smallest", "location": "on the desk"}]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Leo", "in", "the", "study", "and", "tell", "the", "day", "of", "the", "week"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "O"], "slots": [{"intent": "meet", "person": "Leo", "location": "study"}, {"intent": "tell", "content": "day"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "the", "pose", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "laundry", "room", "to", "the", "person", "at", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "content": "pose", "person": "person", "location": "garden table"}]}
{"tokens": ["escort", "the", "standing", "person", "from", "the", "closet", "to", "the", "terrace"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "escort", "filter": "standing", "person": "person", "location": "terrace"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "largest", "object", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "largest", "location": "on the side table"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "what", "day", "is", "today", "to", "the", "waving", "person", "in", "the", "office"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "I-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "content": "day today", "filter": "waving", "person": "person", "location": "office"}]}
{"tokens": ["fetch", "a", "tray", "from", "the", "shelf", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "fetch", "object": "tray", "location": "shelf"}, {"intent": "deliver", "recipient": "me"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "remote", "there", "are", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "remote", "location": "on the shelf"}]}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "drinks", "bar", "then", "meet", "Grace", "and", "say", "something", "about", "yourself"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-CONTENT"], "slots": [{"intent": "go", "location": "drinks bar"}, {"intent": "meet", "person": "Grace"}, {"intent": "say", "content": "yourself"}]}
{"tokens": ["introduce", "yourself", "to", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "red", "t", "shirt", "in", "the", "dining", "area", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"], "slots": [{"intent": "introduce", "person": "red t shirt", "filter": "wearing", "location": "dining area"}, {"intent": "follow"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "the", "gesture", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "laundry", "room", "to", "the", "person", "at", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "content": "gesture", "person": "person", "location": "counter"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "the", "name", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "closet"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "person", "content": "name", "location": "closet"}]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Frank", "in", "the", "bedroom", "and", "take", "them", "to", "the", "balcony"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "meet", "person": "Frank", "location": "bedroom"}, {"intent": "take", "location": "balcony"}]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "right", "arm", "at", "the", "garage"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "follow", "person": "person", "filter": "right arm", "location": "garage"}]}
{"tokens": ["guide", "Noah", "from", "the", "entrance", "to", "the", "bedroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "guide", "person": "Noah", "location": "bedroom"}]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "Rosa", "from", "the", "drinks", "bar", "to", "the", "terrace"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "follow", "person": "Rosa", "location": "terrace"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "the", "pose", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "garden", "to", "the", "person", "at", "the", "laundry", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "content": "pose", "person": "person", "location": "laundry room"}]}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "mug", "in", "the", "laundry", "room", "then", "grasp", "it", "and", "place", "it", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "locate", "object": "mug", "location": "laundry room"}, {"intent": "grasp"}, {"intent": "place", "location": "on the counter"}]}
{"tokens": ["take", "Maria", "from", "the", "shelf", "to", "the", "bathroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "take", "person": "Maria", "location": "bathroom"}]}
{"tokens": ["escort", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "white", "coat", "from", "the", "patio", "to", "the", "storage", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "escort", "person": "white coat", "filter": "wearing", "location": "storage room"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "cups", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "biggest", "object": "cups", "location": "on the shelf"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "smallest", "object", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "smallest", "location": "on the desk"}]}
{"tokens": ["give", "me", "a", "magazine", "from", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "give", "recipient": "me", "object": "magazine", "location": "side table"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "object", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "biggest", "location": "on the desk"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "heaviest", "cans", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "heaviest", "object": "cans", "location": "on the side table"}]}
{"tokens": ["grasp", "a", "cans", "from", "the", "shelf", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "the", "lying", "person", "in", "the", "workshop"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "grasp", "object": "cans", "location": "shelf"}, {"intent": "deliver", "filter": "lying", "recipient": "person", "location": "workshop"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "largest", "object", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "largest", "location": "on the desk"}]}
{"tokens": ["fetch", "a", "books", "from", "the", "shelf", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "Alice", "in", "the", "living", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "fetch", "object": "books", "location": "shelf"}, {"intent": "bring", "recipient": "Alice", "location": "living room"}]}
{"tokens": ["say", "the", "day", "of", "the", "week", "to", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "left", "arm", "in", "the", "bathroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "say", "content": "day", "person": "person", "filter": "left arm", "location": "bathroom"}]}
{"tokens": ["guide", "the", "lying", "person", "from", "the", "garden", "table", "to", "the", "living", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "guide", "filter": "lying", "person": "person", "location": "living room"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "lightest", "books", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "lightest", "object": "books", "location": "on the shelf"}]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "right", "arm", "in", "the", "dining", "area"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "follow", "person": "person", "filter": "right arm", "location": "dining area"}]}
{"tokens": ["look", "for", "a", "mugs", "in", "the", "entrance", "then", "get", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "the", "sitting", "person", "in", "the", "entrance"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "look", "object": "mugs", "location": "entrance"}, {"intent": "get"}, {"intent": "deliver", "filter": "sitting", "recipient": "person", "location": "entrance"}]}
{"tokens": ["look", "for", "a", "pen", "in", "the", "kitchen", "then", "get", "it", "and", "give", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "look", "object": "pen", "location": "kitchen"}, {"intent": "get"}, {"intent": "give", "recipient": "me"}]}
{"tokens": ["get", "a", "magazines", "from", "the", "side", "table", "and", "give", "it", "to", "Charlie", "in", "the", "office"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "get", "object": "magazines", "location": "side table"}, {"intent": "give", "recipient": "Charlie", "location": "office"}]}
{"tokens": ["answer", "the", "question", "of", "the", "waving", "person", "in", "the", "bathroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "answer", "content": "question", "filter": "waving", "person": "person", "location": "bathroom"}]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "the", "lying", "person", "at", "the", "living", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "follow", "filter": "lying", "person": "person", "location": "living room"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "object", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "biggest", "location": "on the counter"}]}
{"tokens": ["say", "hello", "to", "Jack", "in", "the", "balcony", "and", "say", "your", "teams", "country"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "B-CONTENT", "I-CONTENT", "I-CONTENT"], "slots": [{"intent": "say", "person": "Jack", "location": "balcony"}, {"intent": "say", "content": "your teams country"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "dining", "area", "are", "wearing", "orange", "jackets"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "orange jackets", "location": "dining area", "filter": "wearing"}]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "the", "sitting", "person", "in", "the", "terrace"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "follow", "filter": "sitting", "person": "person", "location": "terrace"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "the", "gesture", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "bedroom", "to", "the", "person", "at", "the", "living", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "content": "gesture", "person": "person", "location": "living room"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "the", "name", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "garage", "to", "the", "person", "at", "the", "balcony"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "content": "name", "person": "person", "location": "balcony"}]}
{"tokens": ["answer", "the", "question", "of", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "right", "in", "the", "study"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "answer", "content": "question", "person": "person", "filter": "pointing", "location": "study"}]}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "can", "in", "the", "study", "then", "grasp", "it", "and", "give", "it", "to", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "left", "in", "the", "study"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "locate", "object": "can", "location": "study"}, {"intent": "grasp"}, {"intent": "give", "recipient": "person", "filter": "pointing", "location": "study"}]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "patio", "then", "find", "a", "charger", "and", "fetch", "it", "and", "give", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "navigate", "location": "patio"}, {"intent": "find", "object": "charger"}, {"intent": "fetch"}, {"intent": "give", "recipient": "me"}]}
{"tokens": ["get", "a", "remotes", "from", "the", "garden", "table", "and", "give", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "get", "object": "remotes", "location": "garden table"}, {"intent": "give", "recipient": "me"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "book", "there", "are", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "book", "location": "on the side table"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "the", "name", "of", "the", "person", "in", "the", "entrance"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "person", "content": "name", "location": "entrance"}]}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "right", "in", "the", "patio", "and", "lead", "them", "to", "the", "bedroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "find", "person": "person", "filter": "pointing", "location": "patio"}, {"intent": "lead", "location": "bedroom"}]}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "cans", "in", "the", "balcony", "then", "take", "it", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "find", "object": "cans", "location": "balcony"}, {"intent": "take"}, {"intent": "bring", "recipient": "me"}]}
{"tokens": ["get", "a", "magazine", "from", "the", "shelf", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "Jack", "in", "the", "office"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "get", "object": "magazine", "location": "shelf"}, {"intent": "bring", "recipient": "Jack", "location": "office"}]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Frank", "at", "the", "drinks", "bar", "then", "find", "them", "in", "the", "living", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "meet", "person": "Frank", "location": "drinks bar"}, {"intent": "find", "location": "living room"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "heaviest", "magazines", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "heaviest", "object": "magazines", "location": "on the side table"}]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "entrance", "then", "locate", "the", "sitting", "person", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-VERB", "O"], "slots": [{"intent": "navigate", "location": "entrance"}, {"intent": "locate", "filter": "sitting", "person": "person"}, {"intent": "follow"}]}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "sitting", "person", "in", "the", "garden", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"], "slots": [{"intent": "find", "filter": "sitting", "person": "person", "location": "garden"}, {"intent": "follow"}]}
{"tokens": ["greet", "Diana", "in", "the", "kitchen", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"], "slots": [{"intent": "greet", "person": "Diana", "location": "kitchen"}, {"intent": "follow"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "can", "there", "are", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "can", "location": "on the counter"}]}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "standing", "person", "in", "the", "kitchen", "and", "say", "your", "teams", "name"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "B-CONTENT", "I-CONTENT", "I-CONTENT"], "slots": [{"intent": "find", "filter": "standing", "person": "person", "location": "kitchen"}, {"intent": "say", "content": "your teams name"}]}
{"tokens": ["bring", "me", "a", "glass", "from", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "bring", "recipient": "me", "object": "glass", "location": "garden table"}]}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "magazines", "in", "the", "bathroom", "then", "get", "it", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "locate", "object": "magazines", "location": "bathroom"}, {"intent": "get"}, {"intent": "bring", "recipient": "me"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "heaviest", "magazines", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "heaviest", "object": "magazines", "location": "on the counter"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "smallest", "cans", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "smallest", "object": "cans", "location": "on the shelf"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "bottle", "there", "are", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "bottle", "location": "on the shelf"}]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "Maria", "from", "the", "side", "table", "to", "the", "storage", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "follow", "person": "Maria", "location": "storage room"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "book", "there", "are", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "book", "location": "on the side table"}]}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "glass", "in", "the", "balcony", "then", "take", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "locate", "object": "glass", "location": "balcony"}, {"intent": "take"}, {"intent": "deliver", "recipient": "me"}]}
{"tokens": ["get", "a", "tablet", "from", "the", "garden", "table", "and", "place", "it", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "get", "object": "tablet", "location": "garden table"}, {"intent": "place", "location": "on the side table"}]}
{"tokens": ["fetch", "a", "charger", "from", "the", "garden", "table", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "Leo", "in", "the", "terrace"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "fetch", "object": "charger", "location": "garden table"}, {"intent": "bring", "recipient": "Leo", "location": "terrace"}]}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "bedroom", "then", "find", "a", "snacks", "and", "take", "it", "and", "put", "it", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "go", "location": "bedroom"}, {"intent": "find", "object": "snacks"}, {"intent": "take"}, {"intent": "put", "location": "on the counter"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "lying", "persons", "are", "in", "the", "storage", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "filter": "lying", "location": "storage room"}]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "drinks", "bar", "then", "meet", "Maria", "and", "lead", "them", "to", "the", "bathroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "navigate", "location": "drinks bar"}, {"intent": "meet", "person": "Maria"}, {"intent": "lead", "location": "bathroom"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "what", "day", "is", "tomorrow", "to", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "right", "in", "the", "kitchen"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "I-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "content": "day tomorrow", "person": "person", "filter": "pointing", "location": "kitchen"}]}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "pen", "in", "the", "entrance", "then", "take", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "Ingrid", "in", "the", "entrance"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "find", "object": "pen", "location": "entrance"}, {"intent": "take"}, {"intent": "deliver", "recipient": "Ingrid", "location": "entrance"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "waving", "persons", "are", "in", "the", "hallway"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "filter": "waving", "location": "hallway"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "entrance", "are", "wearing", "black", "shirts"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "black shirts", "location": "entrance", "filter": "wearing"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "hallway", "are", "wearing", "white", "sweaters"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "white sweaters", "location": "hallway", "filter": "wearing"}]}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "tablet", "in", "the", "study", "then", "fetch", "it", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "the", "sitting", "person", "in", "the", "study"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "find", "object": "tablet", "location": "study"}, {"intent": "fetch"}, {"intent": "bring", "filter": "sitting", "recipient": "person", "location": "study"}]}
{"tokens": ["give", "me", "a", "book", "from", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "give", "recipient": "me", "object": "book", "location": "shelf"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "remote", "there", "are", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "remote", "location": "on the garden table"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "the", "pose", "of", "the", "person", "in", "the", "laundry", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "person", "content": "pose", "location": "laundry room"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "lightest", "mugs", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "lightest", "object": "mugs", "location": "on the counter"}]}
{"tokens": ["look", "for", "a", "bottles", "in", "the", "storage", "room", "then", "fetch", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "left", "in", "the", "storage", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "look", "object": "bottles", "location": "storage room"}, {"intent": "fetch"}, {"intent": "deliver", "recipient": "person", "filter": "pointing", "location": "storage room"}]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "Charlie", "from", "the", "office", "to", "the", "workshop"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "follow", "person": "Charlie", "location": "workshop"}]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "the", "sitting", "person", "in", "the", "study"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "follow", "filter": "sitting", "person": "person", "location": "study"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "toy", "there", "are", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "toy", "location": "on the desk"}]}
{"tokens": ["introduce", "yourself", "to", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "yellow", "t", "shirt", "in", "the", "terrace", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"], "slots": [{"intent": "introduce", "person": "yellow t shirt", "filter": "wearing", "location": "terrace"}, {"intent": "follow"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "the", "name", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "kitchen", "to", "the", "person", "at", "the", "terrace"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "content": "name", "person": "person", "location": "terrace"}]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Bob", "at", "the", "bedroom", "then", "locate", "them", "in", "the", "garden"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "meet", "person": "Bob", "location": "bedroom"}, {"intent": "locate", "location": "garden"}]}
{"tokens": ["say", "something", "about", "yourself", "to", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "right", "in", "the", "laundry", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "say", "content": "yourself", "person": "person", "filter": "pointing", "location": "laundry room"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "living", "room", "are", "wearing", "yellow", "shirts"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "yellow shirts", "location": "living room", "filter": "wearing"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "lightest", "mugs", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "lightest", "object": "mugs", "location": "on the shelf"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "the", "name", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "workshop", "to", "the", "person", "at", "the", "bedroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "content": "name", "person": "person", "location": "bedroom"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "hallway", "are", "wearing", "yellow", "shirts"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "yellow shirts", "location": "hallway", "filter": "wearing"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "magazine", "there", "are", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "magazine", "location": "on the side table"}]}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "toys", "in", "the", "bathroom", "then", "grasp", "it", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "locate", "object": "toys", "location": "bathroom"}, {"intent": "grasp"}, {"intent": "bring", "recipient": "me"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "the", "pose", "of", "the", "person", "in", "the", "drinks", "bar"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "person", "content": "pose", "location": "drinks bar"}]}
{"tokens": ["bring", "me", "a", "tray", "from", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "bring", "recipient": "me", "object": "tray", "location": "side table"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "glass", "there", "are", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "glass", "location": "on the counter"}]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Jack", "in", "the", "drinks", "bar", "and", "escort", "them", "to", "the", "hallway"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "meet", "person": "Jack", "location": "drinks bar"}, {"intent": "escort", "location": "hallway"}]}
{"tokens": ["bring", "me", "a", "snack", "from", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "bring", "recipient": "me", "object": "snack", "location": "counter"}]}
{"tokens": ["answer", "the", "quiz", "of", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "left", "arm", "in", "the", "dining", "area"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "answer", "content": "quiz", "person": "person", "filter": "left arm", "location": "dining area"}]}
{"tokens": ["answer", "the", "question", "of", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "left", "arm", "in", "the", "patio"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "answer", "content": "question", "person": "person", "filter": "left arm", "location": "patio"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "the", "pose", "of", "the", "person", "in", "the", "living", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "person", "content": "pose", "location": "living room"}]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "workshop", "then", "look", "for", "a", "plates", "and", "get", "it", "and", "give", "it", "to", "Tom", "in", "the", "patio"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "navigate", "location": "workshop"}, {"intent": "look", "object": "plates"}, {"intent": "get"}, {"intent": "give", "recipient": "Tom", "location": "patio"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "lightest", "cups", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "lightest", "object": "cups", "location": "on the side table"}]}
{"tokens": ["get", "a", "bowl", "from", "the", "garden", "table", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "get", "object": "bowl", "location": "garden table"}, {"intent": "deliver", "recipient": "me"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "kitchen", "are", "wearing", "red", "sweaters"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "red sweaters", "location": "kitchen", "filter": "wearing"}]}
{"tokens": ["get", "a", "magazines", "from", "the", "shelf", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "get", "object": "magazines", "location": "shelf"}, {"intent": "deliver", "recipient": "me"}]}
{"tokens": ["take", "Karen", "from", "the", "hallway", "to", "the", "entrance"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "take", "person": "Karen", "location": "entrance"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "waving", "persons", "are", "in", "the", "hallway"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "filter": "waving", "location": "hallway"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "persons", "pointing", "to", "the", "left", "are", "in", "the", "kitchen"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "filter": "pointing", "location": "kitchen"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "magazines", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "biggest", "object": "magazines", "location": "on the side table"}]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Ingrid", "in", "the", "dining", "area", "and", "escort", "them", "to", "the", "bedroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "meet", "person": "Ingrid", "location": "dining area"}, {"intent": "escort", "location": "bedroom"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "heaviest", "remotes", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "heaviest", "object": "remotes", "location": "on the counter"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "remote", "there", "are", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "remote", "location": "on the shelf"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "can", "there", "are", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "can", "location": "on the shelf"}]}
{"tokens": ["guide", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "right", "from", "the", "garden", "to", "the", "patio"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "guide", "person": "person", "filter": "pointing", "location": "patio"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "smallest", "remotes", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "smallest", "object": "remotes", "location": "on the side table"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "thinnest", "object", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "thinnest", "location": "on the counter"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "heaviest", "object", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "heaviest", "location": "on the side table"}]}
{"tokens": ["answer", "the", "quiz", "of", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "right", "arm", "in", "the", "patio"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "answer", "content": "quiz", "person": "person", "filter": "right arm", "location": "patio"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "thinnest", "object", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "thinnest", "location": "on the counter"}]}
{"tokens": ["say", "hello", "to", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "white", "coat", "in", "the", "entrance", "and", "answer", "a", "quiz"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT"], "slots": [{"intent": "say", "person": "white coat", "filter": "wearing", "location": "entrance"}, {"intent": "answer", "content": "quiz"}]}
{"tokens": ["introduce", "yourself", "to", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "white", "coat", "in", "the", "terrace", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"], "slots": [{"intent": "introduce", "person": "white coat", "filter": "wearing", "location": "terrace"}, {"intent": "follow"}]}
{"tokens": ["look", "for", "a", "charger", "in", "the", "kitchen", "then", "grasp", "it", "and", "give", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "look", "object": "charger", "location": "kitchen"}, {"intent": "grasp"}, {"intent": "give", "recipient": "me"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "lightest", "object", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "lightest", "location": "on the desk"}]}
{"tokens": ["look", "for", "a", "lying", "person", "in", "the", "office", "and", "answer", "a", "quiz"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT"], "slots": [{"intent": "look", "filter": "lying", "person": "person", "location": "office"}, {"intent": "answer", "content": "quiz"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "heaviest", "object", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "heaviest", "location": "on the counter"}]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "office", "then", "locate", "a", "glasses", "and", "grasp", "it", "and", "give", "it", "to", "Rosa", "in", "the", "study"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "navigate", "location": "office"}, {"intent": "locate", "object": "glasses"}, {"intent": "grasp"}, {"intent": "give", "recipient": "Rosa", "location": "study"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "bottle", "there", "are", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "bottle", "location": "on the shelf"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "the", "gesture", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "person", "content": "gesture", "location": "side table"}]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Noah", "in", "the", "hallway", "and", "follow", "them", "to", "the", "terrace"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "meet", "person": "Noah", "location": "hallway"}, {"intent": "follow", "location": "terrace"}]}
{"tokens": ["answer", "the", "quiz", "of", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "right", "in", "the", "balcony"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "answer", "content": "quiz", "person": "person", "filter": "pointing", "location": "balcony"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "largest", "object", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "largest", "location": "on the shelf"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "kitchen", "are", "wearing", "black", "shirts"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "black shirts", "location": "kitchen", "filter": "wearing"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "study", "are", "wearing", "white", "t", "shirts"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "white t shirts", "location": "study", "filter": "wearing"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "cup", "there", "are", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "cup", "location": "on the side table"}]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Rosa", "at", "the", "study", "then", "look", "for", "them", "in", "the", "office"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "meet", "person": "Rosa", "location": "study"}, {"intent": "look", "location": "office"}]}
{"tokens": ["say", "your", "teams", "affiliation", "to", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "right", "in", "the", "laundry", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "say", "person": "person", "filter": "pointing", "location": "laundry room"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "magazine", "there", "are", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "magazine", "location": "on the shelf"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "smallest", "object", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "smallest", "location": "on the side table"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "heaviest", "object", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "heaviest", "location": "on the shelf"}]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "Alice", "from", "the", "counter", "to", "the", "drinks", "bar"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "follow", "person": "Alice", "location": "drinks bar"}]}
{"tokens": ["escort", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "gray", "coat", "from", "the", "balcony", "to", "the", "closet"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "escort", "person": "gray coat", "filter": "wearing", "location": "closet"}]}
{"tokens": ["get", "a", "toys", "from", "the", "shelf", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "the", "waving", "person", "in", "the", "closet"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "get", "object": "toys", "location": "shelf"}, {"intent": "bring", "filter": "waving", "recipient": "person", "location": "closet"}]}
{"tokens": ["guide", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "black", "sweater", "from", "the", "kitchen", "to", "the", "laundry", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "guide", "person": "black sweater", "filter": "wearing", "location": "laundry room"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "what", "day", "is", "today", "to", "the", "waving", "person", "in", "the", "hallway"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "I-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "content": "day today", "filter": "waving", "person": "person", "location": "hallway"}]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "the", "standing", "person", "at", "the", "workshop"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "follow", "filter": "standing", "person": "person", "location": "workshop"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "the", "time", "to", "the", "waving", "person", "in", "the", "bedroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "content": "time", "filter": "waving", "person": "person", "location": "bedroom"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "closet", "are", "wearing", "yellow", "blouses"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "yellow blouses", "location": "closet", "filter": "wearing"}]}
{"tokens": ["say", "hello", "to", "Grace", "in", "the", "hallway", "and", "escort", "them", "to", "the", "patio"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "say", "person": "Grace", "location": "hallway"}, {"intent": "escort", "location": "patio"}]}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "sitting", "person", "in", "the", "hallway", "and", "follow", "them", "to", "the", "patio"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "find", "filter": "sitting", "person": "person", "location": "hallway"}, {"intent": "follow", "location": "patio"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "object", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "biggest", "location": "on the desk"}]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Alice", "at", "the", "workshop", "then", "look", "for", "them", "in", "the", "terrace"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "meet", "person": "Alice", "location": "workshop"}, {"intent": "look", "location": "terrace"}]}
{"tokens": ["guide", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "blue", "shirt", "from", "the", "counter", "to", "the", "drinks", "bar"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "guide", "person": "blue shirt", "filter": "wearing", "location": "drinks bar"}]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "laundry", "room", "then", "locate", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "left", "and", "follow", "them", "to", "the", "drinks", "bar"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "navigate", "location": "laundry room"}, {"intent": "locate", "person": "person", "filter": "pointing", "location": "left"}, {"intent": "follow", "location": "drinks bar"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "largest", "object", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "largest", "location": "on the shelf"}]}
{"tokens": ["look", "for", "a", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "left", "in", "the", "garage", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"], "slots": [{"intent": "look", "person": "person", "filter": "pointing", "location": "garage"}, {"intent": "follow"}]}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "patio", "then", "look", "for", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "left", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"], "slots": [{"intent": "go", "location": "patio"}, {"intent": "look", "person": "person", "filter": "pointing", "location": "left"}, {"intent": "follow"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "workshop", "are", "wearing", "red", "t", "shirts"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "red t shirts", "location": "workshop", "filter": "wearing"}]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Eva", "in", "the", "terrace", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"], "slots": [{"intent": "meet", "person": "Eva", "location": "terrace"}, {"intent": "follow"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "the", "pose", "of", "the", "person", "in", "the", "storage", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "person", "content": "pose", "location": "storage room"}]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "balcony", "then", "look", "for", "a", "snack", "and", "grasp", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "navigate", "location": "balcony"}, {"intent": "look", "object": "snack"}, {"intent": "grasp"}, {"intent": "deliver", "recipient": "me"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "mug", "there", "are", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "mug", "location": "on the side table"}]}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "terrace", "then", "look", "for", "a", "charger", "and", "take", "it", "and", "give", "it", "to", "Bob", "in", "the", "garage"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "go", "location": "terrace"}, {"intent": "look", "object": "charger"}, {"intent": "take"}, {"intent": "give", "recipient": "Bob", "location": "garage"}]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Charlie", "in", "the", "garden", "and", "tell", "what", "day", "is", "tomorrow"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "I-CONTENT"], "slots": [{"intent": "meet", "person": "Charlie", "location": "garden"}, {"intent": "tell", "content": "day tomorrow"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "lightest", "object", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "lightest", "location": "on the side table"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "book", "there", "are", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "book", "location": "on the desk"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "bedroom", "are", "wearing", "red", "coats"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "red coats", "location": "bedroom", "filter": "wearing"}]}
{"tokens": ["greet", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "black", "coat", "in", "the", "workshop", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"], "slots": [{"intent": "greet", "person": "black coat", "filter": "wearing", "location": "workshop"}, {"intent": "follow"}]}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "cans", "in", "the", "office", "then", "take", "it", "and", "place", "it", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "locate", "object": "cans", "location": "office"}, {"intent": "take"}, {"intent": "place", "location": "on the desk"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "mugs", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "biggest", "object": "mugs", "location": "on the garden table"}]}
{"tokens": ["guide", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "right", "arm", "from", "the", "garden", "table", "to", "the", "living", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "guide", "person": "person", "filter": "right arm", "location": "living room"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "can", "there", "are", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "can", "location": "on the side table"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "object", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "biggest", "location": "on the garden table"}]}
{"tokens": ["look", "for", "a", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "left", "in", "the", "hallway", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"], "slots": [{"intent": "look", "person": "person", "filter": "pointing", "location": "hallway"}, {"intent": "follow"}]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "workshop", "then", "find", "a", "bottles", "and", "grasp", "it", "and", "put", "it", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "navigate", "location": "workshop"}, {"intent": "find", "object": "bottles"}, {"intent": "grasp"}, {"intent": "put", "location": "on the desk"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "thinnest", "mugs", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "thinnest", "object": "mugs", "location": "on the shelf"}]}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "entrance", "then", "find", "a", "charger", "and", "get", "it", "and", "give", "it", "to", "Alice", "in", "the", "balcony"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "go", "location": "entrance"}, {"intent": "find", "object": "charger"}, {"intent": "get"}, {"intent": "give", "recipient": "Alice", "location": "balcony"}]}
{"tokens": ["take", "a", "pen", "from", "the", "garden", "table", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "the", "standing", "person", "in", "the", "garage"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "take", "object": "pen", "location": "garden table"}, {"intent": "deliver", "filter": "standing", "recipient": "person", "location": "garage"}]}
{"tokens": ["guide", "Hector", "from", "the", "dining", "area", "to", "the", "drinks", "bar"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "guide", "person": "Hector", "location": "drinks bar"}]}
{"tokens": ["look", "for", "a", "standing", "person", "in", "the", "bathroom", "and", "lead", "them", "to", "the", "office"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "look", "filter": "standing", "person": "person", "location": "bathroom"}, {"intent": "lead", "location": "office"}]}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "standing", "person", "in", "the", "dining", "area", "and", "tell", "something", "about", "yourself"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-CONTENT"], "slots": [{"intent": "find", "filter": "standing", "person": "person", "location": "dining area"}, {"intent": "tell", "content": "yourself"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "hallway", "are", "wearing", "red", "coats"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "red coats", "location": "hallway", "filter": "wearing"}]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Tom", "in", "the", "patio", "and", "answer", "a", "question"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT"], "slots": [{"intent": "meet", "person": "Tom", "location": "patio"}, {"intent": "answer", "content": "question"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "thinnest", "bottles", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "thinnest", "object": "bottles", "location": "on the desk"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "lightest", "object", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "lightest", "location": "on the garden table"}]}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "terrace", "then", "locate", "a", "snacks", "and", "take", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "right", "arm", "in", "the", "kitchen"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "go", "location": "terrace"}, {"intent": "locate", "object": "snacks"}, {"intent": "take"}, {"intent": "deliver", "recipient": "person", "filter": "right arm", "location": "kitchen"}]}
{"tokens": ["get", "a", "magazines", "from", "the", "garden", "table", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "the", "sitting", "person", "in", "the", "workshop"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "get", "object": "magazines", "location": "garden table"}, {"intent": "deliver", "filter": "sitting", "recipient": "person", "location": "workshop"}]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "garden", "table", "then", "locate", "a", "mugs", "and", "fetch", "it", "and", "put", "it", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "navigate", "location": "garden table"}, {"intent": "locate", "object": "mugs"}, {"intent": "fetch"}, {"intent": "put", "location": "on the desk"}]}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "living", "room", "then", "meet", "Jack", "and", "escort", "them", "to", "the", "garden"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "go", "location": "living room"}, {"intent": "meet", "person": "Jack"}, {"intent": "escort", "location": "garden"}]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "dining", "area", "then", "look", "for", "a", "magazines", "and", "get", "it", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "Eva", "in", "the", "closet"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "navigate", "location": "dining area"}, {"intent": "look", "object": "magazines"}, {"intent": "get"}, {"intent": "bring", "recipient": "Eva", "location": "closet"}]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "storage", "room", "then", "locate", "a", "snacks", "and", "grasp", "it", "and", "put", "it", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "navigate", "location": "storage room"}, {"intent": "locate", "object": "snacks"}, {"intent": "grasp"}, {"intent": "put", "location": "on the side table"}]}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "key", "in", "the", "garage", "then", "fetch", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "find", "object": "key", "location": "garage"}, {"intent": "fetch"}, {"intent": "deliver", "recipient": "me"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "object", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "biggest", "location": "on the shelf"}]}
{"tokens": ["look", "for", "a", "magazines", "in", "the", "balcony", "then", "get", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "the", "sitting", "person", "in", "the", "balcony"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "look", "object": "magazines", "location": "balcony"}, {"intent": "get"}, {"intent": "deliver", "filter": "sitting", "recipient": "person", "location": "balcony"}]}
{"tokens": ["answer", "the", "question", "of", "the", "waving", "person", "in", "the", "dining", "area"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "answer", "content": "question", "filter": "waving", "person": "person", "location": "dining area"}]}
{"tokens": ["say", "hello", "to", "Frank", "in", "the", "study", "and", "answer", "a", "question"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT"], "slots": [{"intent": "say", "person": "Frank", "location": "study"}, {"intent": "answer", "content": "question"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "object", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "biggest", "location": "on the garden table"}]}
{"tokens": ["take", "Bob", "from", "the", "office", "to", "the", "drinks", "bar"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "take", "person": "Bob", "location": "drinks bar"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "bottle", "there", "are", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "bottle", "location": "on the shelf"}]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "Jack", "from", "the", "garage", "to", "the", "workshop"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "follow", "person": "Jack", "location": "workshop"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "bottle", "there", "are", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "bottle", "location": "on the side table"}]}
{"tokens": ["escort", "the", "lying", "person", "from", "the", "kitchen", "to", "the", "dining", "area"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "escort", "filter": "lying", "person": "person", "location": "dining area"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "lying", "persons", "are", "in", "the", "patio"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "filter": "lying", "location": "patio"}]}
{"tokens": ["salute", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "white", "t", "shirt", "in", "the", "bathroom", "and", "answer", "a", "question"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT"], "slots": [{"intent": "salute", "person": "white t shirt", "filter": "wearing", "location": "bathroom"}, {"intent": "answer", "content": "question"}]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Rosa", "in", "the", "living", "room", "and", "answer", "a", "quiz"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT"], "slots": [{"intent": "meet", "person": "Rosa", "location": "living room"}, {"intent": "answer", "content": "quiz"}]}
{"tokens": ["bring", "me", "a", "glass", "from", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "bring", "recipient": "me", "object": "glass", "location": "counter"}]}
{"tokens": ["say", "hello", "to", "Frank", "in", "the", "garage", "and", "follow", "them", "to", "the", "entrance"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "say", "person": "Frank", "location": "garage"}, {"intent": "follow", "location": "entrance"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "lightest", "mugs", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "lightest", "object": "mugs", "location": "on the shelf"}]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "drinks", "bar", "then", "find", "a", "glasses", "and", "get", "it", "and", "place", "it", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "navigate", "location": "drinks bar"}, {"intent": "find", "object": "glasses"}, {"intent": "get"}, {"intent": "place", "location": "on the counter"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "largest", "object", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "largest", "location": "on the side table"}]}
{"tokens": ["grasp", "a", "glasses", "from", "the", "desk", "and", "place", "it", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "grasp", "object": "glasses", "location": "desk"}, {"intent": "place", "location": "on the side table"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "the", "gesture", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "garage", "to", "the", "person", "at", "the", "garden"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "content": "gesture", "person": "person", "location": "garden"}]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "Ingrid", "from", "the", "closet", "to", "the", "terrace"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "follow", "person": "Ingrid", "location": "terrace"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "object", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "biggest", "location": "on the counter"}]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Karen", "at", "the", "desk", "then", "locate", "them", "in", "the", "garage"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "meet", "person": "Karen", "location": "desk"}, {"intent": "locate", "location": "garage"}]}
{"tokens": ["answer", "the", "question", "of", "the", "waving", "person", "in", "the", "closet"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "answer", "content": "question", "filter": "waving", "person": "person", "location": "closet"}]}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "left", "in", "the", "hallway", "and", "lead", "them", "to", "the", "bedroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "locate", "person": "person", "filter": "pointing", "location": "hallway"}, {"intent": "lead", "location": "bedroom"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "heaviest", "object", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "heaviest", "location": "on the desk"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "drinks", "bar", "are", "wearing", "blue", "sweaters"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "blue sweaters", "location": "drinks bar", "filter": "wearing"}]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "left", "at", "the", "patio"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "follow", "person": "person", "filter": "pointing", "location": "patio"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "entrance", "are", "wearing", "white", "shirts"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "white shirts", "location": "entrance", "filter": "wearing"}]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Frank", "at", "the", "entrance", "then", "look", "for", "them", "in", "the", "workshop"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "meet", "person": "Frank", "location": "entrance"}, {"intent": "look", "location": "workshop"}]}
{"tokens": ["look", "for", "a", "person", "raising", "their", "right", "arm", "in", "the", "dining", "area", "and", "say", "the", "day", "of", "the", "month"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "O"], "slots": [{"intent": "look", "person": "person", "filter": "right arm", "location": "dining area"}, {"intent": "say", "content": "day"}]}
{"tokens": ["answer", "the", "question", "of", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "right", "in", "the", "workshop"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "answer", "content": "question", "person": "person", "filter": "pointing", "location": "workshop"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "lightest", "mugs", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "lightest", "object": "mugs", "location": "on the side table"}]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Charlie", "at", "the", "bedroom", "then", "look", "for", "them", "in", "the", "storage", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "meet", "person": "Charlie", "location": "bedroom"}, {"intent": "look", "location": "storage room"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "the", "pose", "of", "the", "person", "in", "the", "entrance"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "person", "content": "pose", "location": "entrance"}]}
{"tokens": ["give", "me", "a", "plate", "from", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "give", "recipient": "me", "object": "plate", "location": "counter"}]}
{"tokens": ["introduce", "yourself", "to", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "yellow", "t", "shirt", "in", "the", "drinks", "bar", "and", "say", "your", "teams", "affiliation"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O"], "slots": [{"intent": "introduce", "person": "yellow t shirt", "filter": "wearing", "location": "drinks bar"}, {"intent": "say"}]}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "balcony", "then", "meet", "Charlie", "and", "answer", "a", "question"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT"], "slots": [{"intent": "go", "location": "balcony"}, {"intent": "meet", "person": "Charlie"}, {"intent": "answer", "content": "question"}]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "the", "sitting", "person", "in", "the", "entrance"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "follow", "filter": "sitting", "person": "person", "location": "entrance"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "largest", "object", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "largest", "location": "on the side table"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "remote", "there", "are", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "remote", "location": "on the counter"}]}
{"tokens": ["lead", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "red", "blouse", "from", "the", "dining", "area", "to", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "lead", "person": "red blouse", "filter": "wearing", "location": "garden table"}]}
{"tokens": ["bring", "me", "a", "pen", "from", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "bring", "recipient": "me", "object": "pen", "location": "counter"}]}
{"tokens": ["take", "the", "sitting", "person", "from", "the", "dining", "area", "to", "the", "workshop"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "take", "filter": "sitting", "person": "person", "location": "workshop"}]}
{"tokens": ["answer", "the", "question", "of", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "right", "in", "the", "garden"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "answer", "content": "question", "person": "person", "filter": "pointing", "location": "garden"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "the", "name", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "living", "room", "to", "the", "person", "at", "the", "garage"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "content": "name", "person": "person", "location": "garage"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "glass", "there", "are", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "glass", "location": "on the desk"}]}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "hallway", "then", "find", "the", "standing", "person", "and", "say", "your", "teams", "name"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-VERB", "B-CONTENT", "I-CONTENT", "I-CONTENT"], "slots": [{"intent": "go", "location": "hallway"}, {"intent": "find", "filter": "standing", "person": "person"}, {"intent": "say", "content": "your teams name"}]}
{"tokens": ["give", "me", "a", "tray", "from", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "give", "recipient": "me", "object": "tray", "location": "side table"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "toy", "there", "are", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "object": "toy", "location": "on the counter"}]}
{"tokens": ["salute", "Charlie", "in", "the", "balcony", "and", "follow", "them", "to", "the", "drinks", "bar"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "salute", "person": "Charlie", "location": "balcony"}, {"intent": "follow", "location": "drinks bar"}]}
{"tokens": ["salute", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "yellow", "blouse", "in", "the", "patio", "and", "escort", "them", "to", "the", "bathroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "salute", "person": "yellow blouse", "filter": "wearing", "location": "patio"}, {"intent": "escort", "location": "bathroom"}]}
{"tokens": ["look", "for", "a", "magazines", "in", "the", "bedroom", "then", "fetch", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "the", "lying", "person", "in", "the", "bedroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "look", "object": "magazines", "location": "bedroom"}, {"intent": "fetch"}, {"intent": "deliver", "filter": "lying", "recipient": "person", "location": "bedroom"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "largest", "plates", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "attribute": "largest", "object": "plates", "location": "on the shelf"}]}
{"tokens": ["give", "me", "a", "magazine", "from", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "give", "recipient": "me", "object": "magazine", "location": "shelf"}]}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "notebook", "in", "the", "bedroom", "then", "take", "it", "and", "put", "it", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "locate", "object": "notebook", "location": "bedroom"}, {"intent": "take"}, {"intent": "put", "location": "on the counter"}]}
{"tokens": ["escort", "Alice", "from", "the", "bathroom", "to", "the", "bedroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "escort", "person": "Alice", "location": "bedroom"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "the", "gesture", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "storage", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "person", "content": "gesture", "location": "storage room"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "waving", "persons", "are", "in", "the", "bedroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "filter": "waving", "location": "bedroom"}]}
{"tokens": ["say", "hello", "to", "Sam", "in", "the", "closet", "and", "follow", "them", "to", "the", "balcony"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "say", "person": "Sam", "location": "closet"}, {"intent": "follow", "location": "balcony"}]}
{"tokens": ["answer", "the", "quiz", "of", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "left", "in", "the", "laundry", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "answer", "content": "quiz", "person": "person", "filter": "pointing", "location": "laundry room"}]}
{"tokens": ["introduce", "yourself", "to", "Frank", "in", "the", "laundry", "room", "and", "tell", "the", "day", "of", "the", "week"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "O"], "slots": [{"intent": "introduce", "person": "Frank", "location": "laundry room"}, {"intent": "tell", "content": "day"}]}
{"tokens": ["say", "hello", "to", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "gray", "blouse", "in", "the", "workshop", "and", "lead", "them", "to", "the", "office"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "say", "person": "gray blouse", "filter": "wearing", "location": "workshop"}, {"intent": "lead", "location": "office"}]}
{"tokens": ["bring", "me", "a", "cup", "from", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "slots": [{"intent": "bring", "recipient": "me", "object": "cup", "location": "shelf"}]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "bathroom", "are", "wearing", "blue", "coats"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"], "slots": [{"intent": "tell", "person": "blue coats", "location": "bathroom", "filter": "wearing"}]}
