{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "toys", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "heaviest", "toys", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "bathroom", "then", "locate", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "right", "arm", "and", "guide", "them", "to", "the", "drinks", "bar"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "cans", "in", "the", "bedroom", "then", "get", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "left", "arm", "in", "the", "bedroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "book", "in", "the", "living", "room", "then", "grasp", "it", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["greet", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "yellow", "t", "shirt", "in", "the", "terrace", "and", "guide", "them", "to", "the", "bedroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["lead", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "orange", "jacket", "from", "the", "workshop", "to", "the", "workshop"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["bring", "me", "a", "tablet", "from", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "study", "then", "meet", "Rosa", "and", "say", "your", "teams", "name"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-VERB", "B-CONTENT", "I-CONTENT", "I-CONTENT"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "plate", "there", "are", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "thinnest", "object", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "lightest", "object", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "standing", "person", "in", "the", "closet", "and", "escort", "them", "to", "the", "workshop"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "desk", "then", "locate", "a", "cans", "and", "get", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "Karen", "in", "the", "storage", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "smallest", "object", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["salute", "the", "person", "wearing", "an", "orange", "t", "shirt", "in", "the", "laundry", "room", "and", "tell", "the", "time"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT"]}
{"tokens": ["get", "a", "remotes", "from", "the", "desk", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "the", "pose", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "garden", "table", "to", "the", "person", "at", "the", "bathroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "bottle", "there", "are", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["grasp", "a", "plates", "from", "the", "desk", "and", "place", "it", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "cup", "there", "are", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "closet", "are", "wearing", "blue", "shirts"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "glass", "there", "are", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["escort", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "gray", "t", "shirt", "from", "the", "garage", "to", "the", "office"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["escort", "Sam", "from", "the", "garden", "to", "the", "laundry", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "object", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Tom", "in", "the", "workshop", "and", "follow", "them", "to", "the", "office"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["bring", "me", "a", "plate", "from", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "workshop", "are", "wearing", "orange", "coats"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "study", "then", "find", "a", "box", "and", "grasp", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "Rosa", "in", "the", "workshop"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "largest", "bottles", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "can", "there", "are", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "Olivia", "from", "the", "terrace", "to", "the", "garden"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "thinnest", "mugs", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "lightest", "object", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["take", "a", "bottles", "from", "the", "shelf", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "toy", "in", "the", "study", "then", "get", "it", "and", "place", "it", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "entrance", "are", "wearing", "white", "jackets"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Ingrid", "at", "the", "study", "then", "find", "them", "in", "the", "closet"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "kitchen", "are", "wearing", "white", "t", "shirts"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "smallest", "object", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Leo", "in", "the", "study", "and", "tell", "the", "day", "of", "the", "week"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "the", "pose", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "laundry", "room", "to", "the", "person", "at", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["escort", "the", "standing", "person", "from", "the", "closet", "to", "the", "terrace"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "largest", "object", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "what", "day", "is", "today", "to", "the", "waving", "person", "in", "the", "office"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "I-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["fetch", "a", "tray", "from", "the", "shelf", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "remote", "there", "are", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "drinks", "bar", "then", "meet", "Grace", "and", "say", "something", "about", "yourself"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-CONTENT"]}
{"tokens": ["introduce", "yourself", "to", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "red", "t", "shirt", "in", "the", "dining", "area", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "the", "gesture", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "laundry", "room", "to", "the", "person", "at", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "the", "name", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "closet"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Frank", "in", "the", "bedroom", "and", "take", "them", "to", "the", "balcony"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "right", "arm", "at", "the", "garage"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["guide", "Noah", "from", "the", "entrance", "to", "the", "bedroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "Rosa", "from", "the", "drinks", "bar", "to", "the", "terrace"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "the", "pose", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "garden", "to", "the", "person", "at", "the", "laundry", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "mug", "in", "the", "laundry", "room", "then", "grasp", "it", "and", "place", "it", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["take", "Maria", "from", "the", "shelf", "to", "the", "bathroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["escort", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "white", "coat", "from", "the", "patio", "to", "the", "storage", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "cups", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "smallest", "object", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["give", "me", "a", "magazine", "from", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "object", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "heaviest", "cans", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["grasp", "a", "cans", "from", "the", "shelf", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "the", "lying", "person", "in", "the", "workshop"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "largest", "object", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["fetch", "a", "books", "from", "the", "shelf", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "Alice", "in", "the", "living", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["say", "the", "day", "of", "the", "week", "to", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "left", "arm", "in", "the", "bathroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["guide", "the", "lying", "person", "from", "the", "garden", "table", "to", "the", "living", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "lightest", "books", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "right", "arm", "in", "the", "dining", "area"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["look", "for", "a", "mugs", "in", "the", "entrance", "then", "get", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "the", "sitting", "person", "in", "the", "entrance"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["look", "for", "a", "pen", "in", "the", "kitchen", "then", "get", "it", "and", "give", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["get", "a", "magazines", "from", "the", "side", "table", "and", "give", "it", "to", "Charlie", "in", "the", "office"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["answer", "the", "question", "of", "the", "waving", "person", "in", "the", "bathroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "the", "lying", "person", "at", "the", "living", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "object", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["say", "hello", "to", "Jack", "in", "the", "balcony", "and", "say", "your", "teams", "country"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "B-CONTENT", "I-CONTENT", "I-CONTENT"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "dining", "area", "are", "wearing", "orange", "jackets"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "the", "sitting", "person", "in", "the", "terrace"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "the", "gesture", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "bedroom", "to", "the", "person", "at", "the", "living", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "the", "name", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "garage", "to", "the", "person", "at", "the", "balcony"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["answer", "the", "question", "of", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "right", "in", "the", "study"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "can", "in", "the", "study", "then", "grasp", "it", "and", "give", "it", "to", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "left", "in", "the", "study"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "patio", "then", "find", "a", "charger", "and", "fetch", "it", "and", "give", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["get", "a", "remotes", "from", "the", "garden", "table", "and", "give", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "book", "there", "are", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "the", "name", "of", "the", "person", "in", "the", "entrance"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "right", "in", "the", "patio", "and", "lead", "them", "to", "the", "bedroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "cans", "in", "the", "balcony", "then", "take", "it", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["get", "a", "magazine", "from", "the", "shelf", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "Jack", "in", "the", "office"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Frank", "at", "the", "drinks", "bar", "then", "find", "them", "in", "the", "living", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "heaviest", "magazines", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "entrance", "then", "locate", "the", "sitting", "person", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-VERB", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "sitting", "person", "in", "the", "garden", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["greet", "Diana", "in", "the", "kitchen", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "can", "there", "are", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "standing", "person", "in", "the", "kitchen", "and", "say", "your", "teams", "name"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "B-CONTENT", "I-CONTENT", "I-CONTENT"]}
{"tokens": ["bring", "me", "a", "glass", "from", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "magazines", "in", "the", "bathroom", "then", "get", "it", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "heaviest", "magazines", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "smallest", "cans", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "bottle", "there", "are", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "Maria", "from", "the", "side", "table", "to", "the", "storage", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "book", "there", "are", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "glass", "in", "the", "balcony", "then", "take", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["get", "a", "tablet", "from", "the", "garden", "table", "and", "place", "it", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["fetch", "a", "charger", "from", "the", "garden", "table", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "Leo", "in", "the", "terrace"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "bedroom", "then", "find", "a", "snacks", "and", "take", "it", "and", "put", "it", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "lying", "persons", "are", "in", "the", "storage", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "drinks", "bar", "then", "meet", "Maria", "and", "lead", "them", "to", "the", "bathroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "what", "day", "is", "tomorrow", "to", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "right", "in", "the", "kitchen"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "I-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "pen", "in", "the", "entrance", "then", "take", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "Ingrid", "in", "the", "entrance"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "waving", "persons", "are", "in", "the", "hallway"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "entrance", "are", "wearing", "black", "shirts"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "hallway", "are", "wearing", "white", "sweaters"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "tablet", "in", "the", "study", "then", "fetch", "it", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "the", "sitting", "person", "in", "the", "study"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["give", "me", "a", "book", "from", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "remote", "there", "are", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "the", "pose", "of", "the", "person", "in", "the", "laundry", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "lightest", "mugs", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["look", "for", "a", "bottles", "in", "the", "storage", "room", "then", "fetch", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "left", "in", "the", "storage", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "Charlie", "from", "the", "office", "to", "the", "workshop"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "the", "sitting", "person", "in", "the", "study"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "toy", "there", "are", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["introduce", "yourself", "to", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "yellow", "t", "shirt", "in", "the", "terrace", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "the", "name", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "kitchen", "to", "the", "person", "at", "the", "terrace"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Bob", "at", "the", "bedroom", "then", "locate", "them", "in", "the", "garden"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["say", "something", "about", "yourself", "to", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "right", "in", "the", "laundry", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "living", "room", "are", "wearing", "yellow", "shirts"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "lightest", "mugs", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "the", "name", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "workshop", "to", "the", "person", "at", "the", "bedroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "hallway", "are", "wearing", "yellow", "shirts"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "magazine", "there", "are", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "toys", "in", "the", "bathroom", "then", "grasp", "it", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "the", "pose", "of", "the", "person", "in", "the", "drinks", "bar"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["bring", "me", "a", "tray", "from", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "glass", "there", "are", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Jack", "in", "the", "drinks", "bar", "and", "escort", "them", "to", "the", "hallway"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["bring", "me", "a", "snack", "from", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["answer", "the", "quiz", "of", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "left", "arm", "in", "the", "dining", "area"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["answer", "the", "question", "of", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "left", "arm", "in", "the", "patio"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "the", "pose", "of", "the", "person", "in", "the", "living", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "workshop", "then", "look", "for", "a", "plates", "and", "get", "it", "and", "give", "it", "to", "Tom", "in", "the", "patio"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "lightest", "cups", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["get", "a", "bowl", "from", "the", "garden", "table", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "kitchen", "are", "wearing", "red", "sweaters"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["get", "a", "magazines", "from", "the", "shelf", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["take", "Karen", "from", "the", "hallway", "to", "the", "entrance"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "waving", "persons", "are", "in", "the", "hallway"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "persons", "pointing", "to", "the", "left", "are", "in", "the", "kitchen"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "magazines", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Ingrid", "in", "the", "dining", "area", "and", "escort", "them", "to", "the", "bedroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "heaviest", "remotes", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "remote", "there", "are", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "can", "there", "are", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["guide", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "right", "from", "the", "garden", "to", "the", "patio"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "smallest", "remotes", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "thinnest", "object", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "heaviest", "object", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["answer", "the", "quiz", "of", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "right", "arm", "in", "the", "patio"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "thinnest", "object", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["say", "hello", "to", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "white", "coat", "in", "the", "entrance", "and", "answer", "a", "quiz"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT"]}
{"tokens": ["introduce", "yourself", "to", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "white", "coat", "in", "the", "terrace", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["look", "for", "a", "charger", "in", "the", "kitchen", "then", "grasp", "it", "and", "give", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "lightest", "object", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["look", "for", "a", "lying", "person", "in", "the", "office", "and", "answer", "a", "quiz"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "heaviest", "object", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "office", "then", "locate", "a", "glasses", "and", "grasp", "it", "and", "give", "it", "to", "Rosa", "in", "the", "study"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "bottle", "there", "are", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "the", "gesture", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Noah", "in", "the", "hallway", "and", "follow", "them", "to", "the", "terrace"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["answer", "the", "quiz", "of", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "right", "in", "the", "balcony"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "largest", "object", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "kitchen", "are", "wearing", "black", "shirts"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "study", "are", "wearing", "white", "t", "shirts"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "cup", "there", "are", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Rosa", "at", "the", "study", "then", "look", "for", "them", "in", "the", "office"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["say", "your", "teams", "affiliation", "to", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "right", "in", "the", "laundry", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "magazine", "there", "are", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "smallest", "object", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "heaviest", "object", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "Alice", "from", "the", "counter", "to", "the", "drinks", "bar"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["escort", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "gray", "coat", "from", "the", "balcony", "to", "the", "closet"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["get", "a", "toys", "from", "the", "shelf", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "the", "waving", "person", "in", "the", "closet"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["guide", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "black", "sweater", "from", "the", "kitchen", "to", "the", "laundry", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "what", "day", "is", "today", "to", "the", "waving", "person", "in", "the", "hallway"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "I-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "the", "standing", "person", "at", "the", "workshop"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "the", "time", "to", "the", "waving", "person", "in", "the", "bedroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "closet", "are", "wearing", "yellow", "blouses"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["say", "hello", "to", "Grace", "in", "the", "hallway", "and", "escort", "them", "to", "the", "patio"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "sitting", "person", "in", "the", "hallway", "and", "follow", "them", "to", "the", "patio"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "object", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Alice", "at", "the", "workshop", "then", "look", "for", "them", "in", "the", "terrace"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["guide", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "blue", "shirt", "from", "the", "counter", "to", "the", "drinks", "bar"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "laundry", "room", "then", "locate", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "left", "and", "follow", "them", "to", "the", "drinks", "bar"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "largest", "object", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["look", "for", "a", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "left", "in", "the", "garage", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "patio", "then", "look", "for", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "left", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "workshop", "are", "wearing", "red", "t", "shirts"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Eva", "in", "the", "terrace", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "the", "pose", "of", "the", "person", "in", "the", "storage", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "balcony", "then", "look", "for", "a", "snack", "and", "grasp", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "mug", "there", "are", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "terrace", "then", "look", "for", "a", "charger", "and", "take", "it", "and", "give", "it", "to", "Bob", "in", "the", "garage"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Charlie", "in", "the", "garden", "and", "tell", "what", "day", "is", "tomorrow"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "I-CONTENT"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "lightest", "object", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "book", "there", "are", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "bedroom", "are", "wearing", "red", "coats"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["greet", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "black", "coat", "in", "the", "workshop", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "cans", "in", "the", "office", "then", "take", "it", "and", "place", "it", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "mugs", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["guide", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "right", "arm", "from", "the", "garden", "table", "to", "the", "living", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "can", "there", "are", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "object", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["look", "for", "a", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "left", "in", "the", "hallway", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "workshop", "then", "find", "a", "bottles", "and", "grasp", "it", "and", "put", "it", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "thinnest", "mugs", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "entrance", "then", "find", "a", "charger", "and", "get", "it", "and", "give", "it", "to", "Alice", "in", "the", "balcony"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["take", "a", "pen", "from", "the", "garden", "table", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "the", "standing", "person", "in", "the", "garage"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["guide", "Hector", "from", "the", "dining", "area", "to", "the", "drinks", "bar"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["look", "for", "a", "standing", "person", "in", "the", "bathroom", "and", "lead", "them", "to", "the", "office"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "standing", "person", "in", "the", "dining", "area", "and", "tell", "something", "about", "yourself"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-CONTENT"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "hallway", "are", "wearing", "red", "coats"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Tom", "in", "the", "patio", "and", "answer", "a", "question"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "thinnest", "bottles", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "lightest", "object", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "terrace", "then", "locate", "a", "snacks", "and", "take", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "right", "arm", "in", "the", "kitchen"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["get", "a", "magazines", "from", "the", "garden", "table", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "the", "sitting", "person", "in", "the", "workshop"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "garden", "table", "then", "locate", "a", "mugs", "and", "fetch", "it", "and", "put", "it", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "living", "room", "then", "meet", "Jack", "and", "escort", "them", "to", "the", "garden"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "dining", "area", "then", "look", "for", "a", "magazines", "and", "get", "it", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "Eva", "in", "the", "closet"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "storage", "room", "then", "locate", "a", "snacks", "and", "grasp", "it", "and", "put", "it", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "key", "in", "the", "garage", "then", "fetch", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "object", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["look", "for", "a", "magazines", "in", "the", "balcony", "then", "get", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "the", "sitting", "person", "in", "the", "balcony"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["answer", "the", "question", "of", "the", "waving", "person", "in", "the", "dining", "area"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["say", "hello", "to", "Frank", "in", "the", "study", "and", "answer", "a", "question"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "object", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["take", "Bob", "from", "the", "office", "to", "the", "drinks", "bar"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "bottle", "there", "are", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "Jack", "from", "the", "garage", "to", "the", "workshop"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "bottle", "there", "are", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["escort", "the", "lying", "person", "from", "the", "kitchen", "to", "the", "dining", "area"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "lying", "persons", "are", "in", "the", "patio"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["salute", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "white", "t", "shirt", "in", "the", "bathroom", "and", "answer", "a", "question"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT"]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Rosa", "in", "the", "living", "room", "and", "answer", "a", "quiz"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT"]}
{"tokens": ["bring", "me", "a", "glass", "from", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["say", "hello", "to", "Frank", "in", "the", "garage", "and", "follow", "them", "to", "the", "entrance"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "lightest", "mugs", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "drinks", "bar", "then", "find", "a", "glasses", "and", "get", "it", "and", "place", "it", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "largest", "object", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["grasp", "a", "glasses", "from", "the", "desk", "and", "place", "it", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "the", "gesture", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "garage", "to", "the", "person", "at", "the", "garden"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "Ingrid", "from", "the", "closet", "to", "the", "terrace"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "object", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Karen", "at", "the", "desk", "then", "locate", "them", "in", "the", "garage"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["answer", "the", "question", "of", "the", "waving", "person", "in", "the", "closet"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "left", "in", "the", "hallway", "and", "lead", "them", "to", "the", "bedroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "heaviest", "object", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "drinks", "bar", "are", "wearing", "blue", "sweaters"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "left", "at", "the", "patio"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "entrance", "are", "wearing", "white", "shirts"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Frank", "at", "the", "entrance", "then", "look", "for", "them", "in", "the", "workshop"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["look", "for", "a", "person", "raising", "their", "right", "arm", "in", "the", "dining", "area", "and", "say", "the", "day", "of", "the", "month"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["answer", "the", "question", "of", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "right", "in", "the", "workshop"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "lightest", "mugs", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Charlie", "at", "the", "bedroom", "then", "look", "for", "them", "in", "the", "storage", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "the", "pose", "of", "the", "person", "in", "the", "entrance"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["give", "me", "a", "plate", "from", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["introduce", "yourself", "to", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "yellow", "t", "shirt", "in", "the", "drinks", "bar", "and", "say", "your", "teams", "affiliation"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "balcony", "then", "meet", "Charlie", "and", "answer", "a", "question"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT"]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "the", "sitting", "person", "in", "the", "entrance"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "largest", "object", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "remote", "there", "are", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["lead", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "red", "blouse", "from", "the", "dining", "area", "to", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["bring", "me", "a", "pen", "from", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["take", "the", "sitting", "person", "from", "the", "dining", "area", "to", "the", "workshop"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["answer", "the", "question", "of", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "right", "in", "the", "garden"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "the", "name", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "living", "room", "to", "the", "person", "at", "the", "garage"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "glass", "there", "are", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "hallway", "then", "find", "the", "standing", "person", "and", "say", "your", "teams", "name"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-VERB", "B-CONTENT", "I-CONTENT", "I-CONTENT"]}
{"tokens": ["give", "me", "a", "tray", "from", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "toy", "there", "are", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["salute", "Charlie", "in", "the", "balcony", "and", "follow", "them", "to", "the", "drinks", "bar"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["salute", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "yellow", "blouse", "in", "the", "patio", "and", "escort", "them", "to", "the", "bathroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["look", "for", "a", "magazines", "in", "the", "bedroom", "then", "fetch", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "the", "lying", "person", "in", "the", "bedroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "largest", "plates", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["give", "me", "a", "magazine", "from", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "notebook", "in", "the", "bedroom", "then", "take", "it", "and", "put", "it", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["escort", "Alice", "from", "the", "bathroom", "to", "the", "bedroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "the", "gesture", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "storage", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "waving", "persons", "are", "in", "the", "bedroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["say", "hello", "to", "Sam", "in", "the", "closet", "and", "follow", "them", "to", "the", "balcony"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["answer", "the", "quiz", "of", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "left", "in", "the", "laundry", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["introduce", "yourself", "to", "Frank", "in", "the", "laundry", "room", "and", "tell", "the", "day", "of", "the", "week"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["say", "hello", "to", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "gray", "blouse", "in", "the", "workshop", "and", "lead", "them", "to", "the", "office"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["bring", "me", "a", "cup", "from", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "bathroom", "are", "wearing", "blue", "coats"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["look", "for", "a", "snack", "in", "the", "workshop", "then", "take", "it", "and", "place", "it", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "bottles", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "counter", "then", "find", "the", "sitting", "person", "and", "follow", "them", "to", "the", "storage", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["answer", "the", "question", "of", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "left", "arm", "in", "the", "garage"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "lightest", "books", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["bring", "me", "a", "mug", "from", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "snack", "there", "are", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["greet", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "yellow", "sweater", "in", "the", "storage", "room", "and", "take", "them", "to", "the", "kitchen"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "snack", "there", "are", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "smallest", "object", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "heaviest", "object", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "snack", "there", "are", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "garage", "then", "find", "a", "phone", "and", "grasp", "it", "and", "put", "it", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["take", "a", "pen", "from", "the", "shelf", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "thinnest", "object", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "Olivia", "from", "the", "balcony", "to", "the", "terrace"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Sam", "in", "the", "bedroom", "and", "say", "the", "day", "of", "the", "month"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["salute", "Karen", "in", "the", "hallway", "and", "say", "the", "day", "of", "the", "week"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "largest", "remotes", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "can", "there", "are", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "magazine", "in", "the", "hallway", "then", "grasp", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "Tom", "in", "the", "hallway"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["take", "a", "plates", "from", "the", "side", "table", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "Jack", "in", "the", "storage", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Grace", "at", "the", "bedroom", "then", "look", "for", "them", "in", "the", "living", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["give", "me", "a", "tablet", "from", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["bring", "me", "a", "magazine", "from", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["answer", "the", "quiz", "of", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "right", "in", "the", "kitchen"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "lying", "person", "in", "the", "garden", "and", "answer", "a", "quiz"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "laundry", "room", "are", "wearing", "gray", "blouses"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "the", "name", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "living", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["salute", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "yellow", "shirt", "in", "the", "garage", "and", "answer", "a", "quiz"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT"]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "balcony", "then", "find", "a", "box", "and", "grasp", "it", "and", "give", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["fetch", "a", "remotes", "from", "the", "shelf", "and", "give", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "the", "pose", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "laundry", "room", "to", "the", "person", "at", "the", "dining", "area"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["fetch", "a", "glass", "from", "the", "shelf", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "storage", "room", "are", "wearing", "yellow", "blouses"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["grasp", "a", "notebook", "from", "the", "side", "table", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "Leo", "in", "the", "dining", "area"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "lying", "persons", "are", "in", "the", "drinks", "bar"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "the", "waving", "person", "at", "the", "dining", "area"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "magazines", "in", "the", "kitchen", "then", "get", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "Olivia", "in", "the", "kitchen"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["lead", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "right", "from", "the", "living", "room", "to", "the", "garden"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "waving", "person", "in", "the", "office", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "lightest", "mugs", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["take", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "gray", "blouse", "from", "the", "hallway", "to", "the", "dining", "area"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["look", "for", "a", "waving", "person", "in", "the", "living", "room", "and", "escort", "them", "to", "the", "study"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "entrance", "are", "wearing", "blue", "t", "shirts"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["bring", "me", "a", "mug", "from", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["fetch", "a", "snack", "from", "the", "counter", "and", "give", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "object", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "shelf", "then", "look", "for", "a", "bowl", "and", "grasp", "it", "and", "place", "it", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["introduce", "yourself", "to", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "white", "t", "shirt", "in", "the", "balcony", "and", "tell", "what", "day", "is", "today"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "I-CONTENT"]}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "sitting", "person", "in", "the", "laundry", "room", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "balcony", "are", "wearing", "gray", "jackets"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "thinnest", "remotes", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "smallest", "cans", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["say", "hello", "to", "Sam", "in", "the", "bedroom", "and", "follow", "them", "to", "the", "living", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "plates", "in", "the", "drinks", "bar", "then", "get", "it", "and", "give", "it", "to", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "left", "arm", "in", "the", "drinks", "bar"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "bedroom", "then", "look", "for", "a", "plates", "and", "grasp", "it", "and", "bring", "it", "to", "Maria", "in", "the", "laundry", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "something", "about", "yourself", "to", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "left", "arm", "in", "the", "patio"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Ingrid", "in", "the", "garage", "and", "follow", "them", "to", "the", "terrace"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "Maria", "from", "the", "living", "room", "to", "the", "terrace"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["escort", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "gray", "shirt", "from", "the", "closet", "to", "the", "hallway"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "snacks", "in", "the", "office", "then", "fetch", "it", "and", "place", "it", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "garden", "then", "meet", "Jack", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-VERB", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["fetch", "a", "mugs", "from", "the", "desk", "and", "give", "it", "to", "Rosa", "in", "the", "study"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "Tom", "from", "the", "entrance", "to", "the", "dining", "area"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["introduce", "yourself", "to", "the", "person", "wearing", "an", "orange", "sweater", "in", "the", "laundry", "room", "and", "say", "the", "time"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "sitting", "persons", "are", "in", "the", "laundry", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "waving", "person", "in", "the", "office", "and", "tell", "something", "about", "yourself"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-CONTENT"]}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "study", "then", "look", "for", "the", "sitting", "person", "and", "tell", "your", "teams", "name"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-VERB", "B-CONTENT", "I-CONTENT", "I-CONTENT"]}
{"tokens": ["escort", "Grace", "from", "the", "balcony", "to", "the", "closet"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "the", "lying", "person", "in", "the", "entrance"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "workshop", "then", "meet", "Charlie", "and", "lead", "them", "to", "the", "balcony"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["find", "a", "sitting", "person", "in", "the", "kitchen", "and", "tell", "your", "teams", "name"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "B-CONTENT", "I-CONTENT", "I-CONTENT"]}
{"tokens": ["grasp", "a", "notebook", "from", "the", "counter", "and", "put", "it", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["escort", "Sam", "from", "the", "dining", "area", "to", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "object", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["give", "me", "a", "mug", "from", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["introduce", "yourself", "to", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "white", "t", "shirt", "in", "the", "kitchen", "and", "follow", "them", "to", "the", "garden"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "living", "room", "then", "look", "for", "a", "bottle", "and", "take", "it", "and", "put", "it", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "persons", "pointing", "to", "the", "right", "are", "in", "the", "terrace"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "Quentin", "from", "the", "side", "table", "to", "the", "entrance"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["bring", "me", "a", "notebook", "from", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["introduce", "yourself", "to", "Rosa", "in", "the", "drinks", "bar", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "drinks", "bar", "then", "look", "for", "a", "books", "and", "take", "it", "and", "place", "it", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["navigate", "to", "the", "hallway", "then", "locate", "a", "glasses", "and", "grasp", "it", "and", "place", "it", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "plate", "there", "are", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "sitting", "persons", "are", "in", "the", "closet"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "the", "pose", "of", "the", "person", "in", "the", "entrance"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "the", "pose", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "bathroom", "to", "the", "person", "at", "the", "drinks", "bar"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "office", "then", "look", "for", "a", "snacks", "and", "get", "it", "and", "give", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["take", "a", "cans", "from", "the", "counter", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "Jack", "in", "the", "hallway"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "mug", "there", "are", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "Hector", "from", "the", "entrance", "to", "the", "patio"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "entrance", "then", "locate", "the", "standing", "person", "and", "follow", "them", "to", "the", "office"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["give", "me", "a", "tray", "from", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["give", "me", "a", "book", "from", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Ingrid", "at", "the", "drinks", "bar", "then", "look", "for", "them", "in", "the", "garage"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "lying", "persons", "are", "in", "the", "kitchen"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "Noah", "from", "the", "entrance", "to", "the", "entrance"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["look", "for", "a", "lying", "person", "in", "the", "office", "and", "say", "your", "teams", "country"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "B-CONTENT", "I-CONTENT", "I-CONTENT"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "office", "are", "wearing", "yellow", "jackets"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "what", "day", "is", "today", "to", "the", "waving", "person", "in", "the", "terrace"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "I-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "person", "raising", "their", "left", "arm", "in", "the", "kitchen", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "workshop", "then", "meet", "Quentin", "and", "lead", "them", "to", "the", "garden"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["bring", "me", "a", "phone", "from", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["escort", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "orange", "t", "shirt", "from", "the", "entrance", "to", "the", "living", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "thinnest", "snacks", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "thinnest", "object", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "glass", "there", "are", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "plate", "there", "are", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "smallest", "books", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "largest", "object", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["take", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "gray", "blouse", "from", "the", "laundry", "room", "to", "the", "drinks", "bar"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "heaviest", "plates", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "glass", "there", "are", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["lead", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "white", "coat", "from", "the", "bedroom", "to", "the", "hallway"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "smallest", "toys", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["escort", "the", "standing", "person", "from", "the", "side", "table", "to", "the", "closet"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["guide", "the", "sitting", "person", "from", "the", "closet", "to", "the", "hallway"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["take", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "right", "arm", "from", "the", "study", "to", "the", "entrance"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "smallest", "remotes", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "object", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "smallest", "object", "on", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["give", "me", "a", "can", "from", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "the", "gesture", "of", "the", "person", "at", "the", "terrace", "to", "the", "person", "at", "the", "bedroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "thinnest", "magazines", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Grace", "at", "the", "bedroom", "then", "find", "them", "in", "the", "garage"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "office", "are", "wearing", "black", "jackets"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "magazine", "there", "are", "on", "the", "garden", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["guide", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "left", "arm", "from", "the", "workshop", "to", "the", "laundry", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "laundry", "room", "then", "locate", "a", "cup", "and", "get", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "smallest", "mugs", "on", "the", "counter"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "B-OBJ", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["introduce", "yourself", "to", "the", "person", "wearing", "a", "white", "coat", "in", "the", "garage", "and", "answer", "a", "quiz"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT"]}
{"tokens": ["answer", "the", "quiz", "of", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "right", "arm", "in", "the", "hallway"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["go", "to", "the", "counter", "then", "locate", "the", "waving", "person", "and", "tell", "your", "teams", "country"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-VERB", "B-CONTENT", "I-CONTENT", "I-CONTENT"]}
{"tokens": ["bring", "me", "a", "bottle", "from", "the", "side", "table"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "object", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["grasp", "a", "glasses", "from", "the", "shelf", "and", "give", "it", "to", "me"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "persons", "raising", "their", "left", "arm", "are", "in", "the", "garage"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "lightest", "object", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["locate", "a", "snack", "in", "the", "bathroom", "then", "get", "it", "and", "deliver", "it", "to", "Charlie", "in", "the", "bathroom"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "how", "many", "people", "in", "the", "kitchen", "are", "wearing", "blue", "shirts"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"]}
{"tokens": ["meet", "Hector", "in", "the", "laundry", "room", "and", "follow", "them", "to", "the", "garage"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "Frank", "from", "the", "bathroom", "to", "the", "storage", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["bring", "me", "a", "mug", "from", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "smallest", "object", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["say", "your", "teams", "country", "to", "the", "person", "pointing", "to", "the", "right", "in", "the", "study"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-CONTENT", "I-CONTENT", "I-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["greet", "the", "person", "wearing", "an", "orange", "jacket", "in", "the", "garden", "and", "follow", "them"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["escort", "the", "sitting", "person", "from", "the", "hallway", "to", "the", "living", "room"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-FILTER", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "me", "what", "is", "the", "largest", "object", "on", "the", "shelf"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "I-VERB", "I-VERB", "O", "O", "B-ATTR", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["follow", "Leo", "from", "the", "hallway", "to", "the", "balcony"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["take", "a", "toys", "from", "the", "shelf", "and", "place", "it", "on", "the", "desk"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "O", "B-OBJ", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-VERB", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["tell", "your", "teams", "country", "to", "the", "person", "raising", "their", "right", "arm", "in", "the", "closet"], "labels": ["B-VERB", "B-CONTENT", "I-CONTENT", "I-CONTENT", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-FILTER", "O", "B-FILTER", "I-FILTER", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
